In New York City, there's a fine line between law and chaos.
在~s 法律c混y有明@的界限
On that line live Danson and Highsmith.
在那l界限上的是丹森和海史密斯
Tell me again why I decided to get on this roof!
再f一遍我槭颤N要爬上!
I think you can chalk that up to bad life choices.
我X得你可以w罪於e`的人生x
Get rid of that asshole.
值裟混蛋
Uh-oh!        I hate it when you say "uh-oh!"
啊哦      我你f"啊哦"
Dude, you put a ding in my hood!
老兄 你身手真敏捷!
Come on with it, then!
放R^戆!
That's trouble.
麻┝
Did someone call Nine-One-holy-shit?
l打了九夭夭?
That's it. I'm sick of all this running.
到此Y束了 我倦了逃硖尤
Hang on!
抓o了!
You have the right to remain silent!
你有啾３殖聊
But I wanna hear you scream!
但我想你尖叫!
Down on the ground!
P倒!
Detective! Yeah, yeah! Detective!
探T 嘿 探T
One at a time, all right?
一 好不好?
Yeah, Detectives, Rick Grayson,
探T 我是雷克・格雷森
New York Observer Online.
碜约~s^察者W的者
These suspects were caught with only a quarter pound of marijuana,
@些嫌犯被逮捕r只lF持有0.25磅的大麻
a misdemeanor in some states.
在一些州只算p罪
Do you think this arrest was worth $12 million in property damages?
你J檫@次造成1200fp失的逮捕行又档?
Why don't we let New York City answer that question?
槭颤N不~s回答@}?
The greatest city on Earth, yeah!
@是世界上最好的城市!
Hi, Sarah Gapone from TMZ print edition.
你好 碜TMZ出版社的莎拉・加夫尼
Danson, are the rumors about you and Kim Kardashian true?
丹森 你和金姆・卡丹森的p是真的?
No comment.
我不做u
But, yes.
但 是的
Danson and Highsmith, free hot dogs for life!
丹森和海史密斯 K生都有免M峁烦!
No drinks. No drinks. I can't do it. I can't do it.
但料不免M 我不能太多啊
Danson and Highsmith shoot, drive, and sex with style.
丹森和海史密斯o射 _ 做鄱加行
They're rock stars.
他是明星
Then you got your jokers, your ball busters, your vets...
然後才到v笑的 打球的 Ft
...and the other guys.
和二流人物
We know, we know. We know.
我知道 我知道 我知道
All right, all right, all right. Listen up, listen up!
好好好 我f! 我f!
We're having a celebration tonight at Butter.
今晚我在巴特酒店_c祝
Brody Jenner's gonna be there. Bai Ling.
布_迪・珍妮去 有白`
That little short bitch from Jersey Shore.        Yeah!
碜晌骱０兜男℃蛔      耶!
And most of you are on the list.
你大部分都被邀了
You're the best.
你最棒
Guys, I'm gonna say something right now.
同志 我F在有要f
It's about a man who came from Austria with a dream.
P於一碜W地利的有粝氲娜
Arnold Schwarzenegger!        Let me finish.
阿Z・施瓦辛格!      我f完
He became a champion and then a movie star, all right?
他先成楣谲後碜隽擞靶 懂?
Arnold Schwarzenegger!        God damn it, let me...
阿Z・施瓦辛格!      死 我f...
They ruined the story. They ruined the story.
你Я诉@故事 你Я诉@故事
Let...What...The point is,
重要的是
we couldn't do our job
我]有今天的成就
if it weren't for you guys doing all the paperwork,
如果]有你做文工作
answering the phones, and all that stupid shit that we don't like to do.
接 有其他我不做的事
all the gun fights all the car chases
那些 那些追捕行
all the sex we don't wanna have with women, but we have to,
那些我本不想s又不得不上的女人
all due to what you guys do. Thank you.
都是因橛辛四 xx
And we'd do it again and again.
而且我L而褪嫉刈鲋
Hey, you shut your face!
]上你的臭嘴
If we wanna hear you talk,
如果你要v
I will shove my arm up your ass and work your mouth like a puppet!
我就把手哪闫ㄑ垩Y伸M去 然後把你木偶耍!
You hear me? You hear me?
到了]? 到了]?
Cash bar.        Yeah.
酒吧
Peace out, bitches.
老c 混蛋
Hey, fellas. All right, bring it in.
好 夥 靠近c
Come on. Bring it in a little bit.
戆 靠近c
All right, right there.
@Y就行了
Just back up, just like right there.
後退 就站在@Y
All right, just one...Just a...
好 再退...再前M...
There you go, right there. Right there.
就是@Y 就是@Y
This is their paperwork. You know they're not gonna do it.
@是他的文工作 你知道他不做的
That's right. This paperwork is like Bob's wife here.
]e @些文工作就像U勃的老婆
It's thick, ugly, got Danson's fingerprints all over it.
又厚又o趣 M是丹森的指y
No offense, Bob.        That's all right.
o冒犯之意 U勃      ]PS
Anyway, now who wants it?        I do!
o如何 l要做?      我要!
All right! Paper Bitch and Yankee Clipper on the case!
好的 @活o文y子和P基剪子了!
Nice work. Thanks, Allen.        Thank you, Captain.
好好 xx 艾      xxL官
"I'll do it! I'll do it!"
"o我做 o我做"
Stop humming that song!
e再哼那歌啦!
I can hum if I want to.        No, I know you can.
我想哼就哼      不 我知道你想
I'm asking you to stop.
但我偏要你停
Well, if you're asking, then I'll stop.        Thank you.
如果你要求的 我就停      xx
Could you not smile like that?
你可不可以不那有?
Now you're asking me to mask my emotions
你因樽约旱母星
because of how it makes you feel.
而要求我掩我的感情
That I will not do.
我才不帜
Seriously, stop humming! Okay?
f真的 不要再哼了 好?
This isn't accounting or wherever the hell
@不是y
you and your little pocket calculator were transferred from.
你e以橛媚愕男∮算器就能搞定
Forensic accounting, okay. And it's an important part of the job.
法 好不好 @工作很重要的
Yeah, whatever.
S你便
Stop being so overtly happy about doing shit work, you moron.
做@N垃圾工作就e屁屁的啦 你傻帽
Hey, guys. Reminder.
同志 提醒一下
The police union picnic's coming up this weekend.
警署的野餐聚⒃谶L末ek
My wife's making her famous deviled eggs, again. My waistline's furious.
我老婆要做拿手菜芥末蛋 我的肚子又要未D
It's a bad time, Bob!
F在不f那 U勃
All right.
好吧
Going to get a slice.
去吃K蛋糕
You know what I just did?
你知道我才看到什N了?
I just walked out that door, saw a couple detectives,
我一出T 就看到一些探T
and I was about to start bad mouthing you behind your back,
他R上就要在你背後f脑了
but I stopped myself, because my pops taught me
但是我]有f你脑 因槲野教我
that a man who talks behind somebody's back is a coward.
在背後fe人脑的人是懦夫
Wow, I actually appreciate that.
哇 我很感激
Good, 'cause I'm gonna tell you directly to your face.
好 因槲乙面f你的脑
No. You don't have to.        No, I don't like you.
不 你不必        不 我不喜g你
I think you're a fake cop.
我X得你不是真警察
The sound of your piss hitting the urinal? It sounds feminine.
你小便r候的音 起砀娘似的
If we were in the wild, I would attack you.
如果在野外 我攻裟愕
Even if you weren't in my food chain,
哪怕你不在我的食物Y
I would go out of my way to attack you.
我也破例把你o宰了
If I were a lion, and you were a tuna,
如果我是雄{ 你是金~
I would swim out in the middle of the ocean and freaking eat you!
我游在海中把你吃掉
And then I'd bang your tuna girlfriend.
然後上你的女友
Okay, first off, a lion swimming in the ocean?
首先 怎N有游泳的{子?
Lions don't like water.
{子不喜g水
If you'd placed it near a river or some sort of fresh water source,
你硬把它放在河流或者淡水的旁
that'd make sense.
倒是行得通
But you find yourself in the ocean, 20-foot waves,
但假使你在海中 二十英尺高的巨浪
I'm assuming it's off the coast of South Africa,
我f的是在南非的海域
coming up against a full-grown, 800-pound tuna
遇到一八百磅的成年金~
with his 20 or 30 friends?
有他的二三十朋友
You lose that battle.
你必死o疑
You lose that battle nine times out of ten. And guess what?
你十有八九死的 你知道?
You've wandered into our school of tuna,
如果你敢M入金~群
and we now have a taste of lion.
我就可以L到{子的味道了
We've talked to ourselves. We've communicated.
我和自己v 我交
Yeah?        And said, " You know what?
是      然後f"你知道?
"Lion tastes good. Let's go get some more lion. "
"{子味道不e 我再去吃吧"
We've developed a system to establish a beachhead
我就在╊^建立一基地
and aggressively hunt you and your family.
然後Q食你的整族群
And we will corner your pride,
我Z走你的傲
your children, your offspring.        How you gonna do that?
你的孩子 你的後代      你怎N做?
We will construct a series of breathing apparatus with kelp.
我用海草做一套呼吸b置
We will be able to trap certain amounts of oxygen.
用砦收一些氧
It's not gonna be days at a time,
一次m然不能上岸滋
but an hour, hour 45, no problem.
但一小r^]}
That will give us enough time to figure out where you live,
@游就可以找出你住在哪Y
go back to the sea, get more oxygen, and then stalk you.
回到海洋 z入更多氧 然後再跟你
You just lost at your own game. You're outgunned and outmanned.
你搬石^砸自己的_ 我武器 人刀急饶多
Did that go the way you thought it was gonna go?
你_始是@N想的?
Nope.
不
Two minutes before the markets open,
在_市的煞昼前
Pamela Boardman, CEO of Lendl Global,
帕米拉・博德曼 m道h球公司的裁
ringing the opening bell.
按宣咽鲩_放
With Boardman is investment banker, David Ershon,
博德曼旁的是投Yy行家  大l・厄森
who manages 40% of Lendl's $70-billion equity pool.
他碛刑m道集F七百|Ya的百分之四十
How much did we lose?
我p了多少?
You may ring the bell now, Ms. Boardman.
F在您可以按了 博德曼女士
$32.        Million?
三千砂      f?
No, billion.
不 三百二十|
Shit!
去你的!
Chinatown. Three Triad gang members. I popped two of them off the draw.
唐人街的三黑推ψ 我值袅
Bang, bang.        Yeah.
崩崩      好
Then I raise up to take the leader out.
然後我站起值羲的老大
Shit, I feel like I'm there now.
呀 我好像身R其境
I hear a whistle. My partner's on the roof.
我到口哨 我的搭n在屋
He says, "Let's even the odds!"
他f"我槊癯害"
He tosses me down a Mossberg pump. I send one through his chest.
他把用步把我舻 我直接一穿膛⑺打死
Game over, bitches.
[蚪Y束了 混蛋
All right.        Yeah.
好了      好
Jimmy? Let's talk about how that story made you feel.
吉米? ff那故事令你感X如何?
Like my cock was made out of concrete.
好像我的下w是用混凝土做的
I know it's very tempting.
我知道你很勇敢
You want to impress your friends.
你想令朋友印象深刻
But this is serious stuff we're dealing with, okay?
但是我f的是烂C的} 好不好?
This is firing your weapon in the line of duty.
要按照使用武器
Officer Hoitz?
霍警T?
Oh, man.
哦 天啊
Come on!        Here we go.
有]搞e      要_始了
Would you like to share?
你想分享你的故事?
No, I'd rather not.
不 算了吧
Officer Hoitz, you've been coming here for six months now,
霍警T 你砭署六月了
and you haven't said a word.
始K一言不l
This is a safe room, no judgment here.
@Y很和C的 ]人δ阏f三道四
Jerkoff.
蠢蛋
That's judgment, Jimmy. Come on.
你在ue人 吉米 f吧
I relive it every night.
我每晚都想起
Bronx, October.
布朗克斯^ 十月
Game 7 of the World Series.
世界I棒球\速第七
For all the marbles. High pressure, unruly crowd,
那些大理石 巨大的毫 }y的人群
and I pulled tunnel duty.
我在一隧道Y糖
I mean, I saw a shadowy figure in the tunnel. I told him to stop.
我在隧道看到一黑影 我警告他停下
Whoa, whoa, whoa, this is a restricted area!
嘿 嘿 嘿 @Y禁止通行
Finally pulled my gun.
最後是拿出
Pulled a deadly weapon. He started running at me.
拿出一致命武器 他向我跑
Don't make me shoot! I'll do it!
不要我_! 我的!
Are you deaf? You hear me yell, "Freeze"?
你@了? 我f了"不S"
You dick! I'm Derek Jeter! You shot me!
你混蛋! 我是德Y克・芴 你糁形伊!
You cost me 20 grand on that game!        Douche bag.
你我了二十美金!      混蛋
Cost the city a championship.
~s失去了一座冠啊
I was being groomed for a top position in homicide.
我本硪被提拔到⒔M的高
Now I'm stuck with a desk jockey partner.
F在和一做案^工作的傻子搭n
Everybody calls me the Yankee Clipper.
每人都叫我P基剪子
Because you shot Derek Jeter!
因槟闵渲辛说卵Y克・芴
He's a biracial angel.
他可是p族天使
You should've shot A-Rod.
你向A_德_
Yo, Paper Bitch.
嗨 文y子
What's up, man?        Hey. Hey, guys.
有事?      夥
Paper Bitch.        Paper Bitch.
文y子      文y子
I don't like that, actually.
我不喜g@外
I know you guys think it's fun, but I don't like that name.
我知道你X得有趣 但我不喜g
Still working on the Danson and Highsmith paperwork?
在做丹森和海史密斯的文工作啊?
Shit.        No, actually, actually, that's...
死      不 其 其 那是...
What is this? That looks stupid.
@是什N? 看起砩道舶蛇蟮
Guys, it's illegal permitting for construction.
非法建B工程的批准令
Specifically, scaffolding.
蚀_f是_手架}
Some of the guys were talking.
有些人f
They were like, " How come you've never
你在k公室怎N
fired your weapon in the office before?"
]有用^武器?
Good point.
f的好
I'm sorry, I don't follow.
Σ黄 我不懂
You've never fired your weapon in the office.
你在k公室]有用^武器
We all have, you know. It's called a desk pop.
我都用^ 叫做跳桌
Fellas, look, I know you don't respect me as a police officer.
同志 我知道你不尊重我的工作
Not true.        I'm not stupid.
才]有呢      我不笨
I'm not gonna discharge my firearm in the office.
我在k公室不卸下武器
Gamble, listen to me. I'll try to make it real clear.
甘博 我f 我再f清楚c
We honor the flag,
我很尊重你
and you crap on it when you don't shoot your gun in the office.
你要是不_你就Σ黄鹞
Jimmy. When's the last time you had a desk pop?
吉米 你上次_是什Nr候
September '08.
九月八
Be a man. Do it.        Now.
像男人一 _      F在
Please, please, do it.        Pop one off!
_吧      痛快!
There you go. Pop it off!        Don't think, just go!
]e _      想也e想 _就是了
Here we go.        Do it, yes.
好吧      _
He did it!
他_了
Hey! Shots fired!
嘿 有人_了
Hey, Terry, I did it! I did my first desk pop!
嘿特Y! 我做到了! 我跳桌啦!
It's a real thing, right?
我真的_了 是?
A desk pop?        Yeah.
跳桌?      是
No, that's not real!
]@回事
They were so convincing in their argument, they swung me.
他很有f服力啊 他_了我!
All right, Allen, you're gonna have to hand over your gun.
好吧艾 你必交出
Yes, sir.
遵命L官
Captain, you really wanna disarm this guy,
L官 你要真的想U械
take out the batteries in the calculator.
就把他算器Y的池卸了
All right, I'm gonna give you this. This is a dummy gun.
好吧 o你@ 假
I use it for ceremony.
我日Y用它做做幼
There.
o
You get this back when I feel you know how to handle it.
等你知道怎N使用了再o你
Listen, guys. I'm working two jobs. I'm working here.
著 夥 我有煞莨ぷ 我在@Y有工作
And I got another job at Bed Bath and Beyond. Okay?
在床上用品店那有份工作 好不?
I'm doing that just to put a kid through NYU
我只是想一孩子上~s大W
so he can explore his bisexuality and become a deejay.
他可以探索p性向然後成橐DJ
Now the last thing I need is a ballistics report in the unit.
最後一要求就是警署的道蟾
I'm just gonna ask you guys, please, come on, really.
我不要求你...真的
Just think about...Just be smart.
想想...明c
211 in progress.
l生武b劫
They're using a wrecking ball to clean out Castien Jewelry.
劫匪用大F球砸_了卡斯蒂珠店
All right, we got it.
好了 我知道了
Good luck, guys. Have a good one.        Allen, let's go.
祝你好\ 好好      艾 我走
No, I got work to do.        What? This is work!
不 我有活]干      什N @才是正事
Hey, yo! Danson and Highsmith. We roll in heavy.
丹森和海史密斯 我LL
You cream puffs, sit tight.
你原地乖乖呆
You gotta be shitting me!
你在搞什N鬼!
You can't keep me cooped up in here, okay?
你不能永h把我P在@Y 好不好?
I am a peacock! You gotta let me fly!
我是孔雀 我要w
Did he just...Did he just call himself a peacock?
他管自己叫孔雀?
Let's go! Let's go!
走吧 走吧
Come on, fellas!
放R戆
Wednesday night is taco night at Rikers Island!
L三晚上去R克uOz吃玉米卷吧!
That's the second one this week!
那是本周第二了!
Hey, you monkeys! Stop!
你@些小兔崽子! 不要跑!
Let's go!
快走!
Yeah!
好
Heads up!
抬^!
Shit.
死
Special Forces zipline.
特N部高空滑行
Cut that line! Cut it! Let's go!
切掉那根 切掉! 我走!
These guys are pros.        Let's go!
@些歹徒是＜      我上
You thinking what I'm thinking, partner?
你和我想的一 搭n?
Aim for the bushes.
朝著灌木蔡
Cops still argue to this day why Danson and Highsmith jumped.
警察在楹蔚ど和海史密斯跳了下去
Maybe it was just pride, having survived so many brushes with death.
也S是因轵傲 那N多次死Y逃生
Maybe their egos pushed them off.
也S是他太自了
I don't know. But that shit was crazy.
我不知道 但他真狂
Either way, there was a hole in New York City,
o如何 ~s出F了一洞
and it needed to be filled.
需要人硖M
Two days ago, this city wept.
商烨 ~s哭了
We lost two heroes who gave everything for us,
我失去了奉I了一切的擅英雄
who paid that ultimate sacrifice
他最後的奚
so that we may walk these streets safely.
也是榱宋能虬踩地走在R路上
There wasn't even an awning in their direction.
他跳下去的地方B一遮雨棚都]有
No, I know.        They just jumped 20 stories.
不 我知道      他亩十翘了下
Doesn't make sense, does it?
@不符合 ?
I only hope God lets them take their. 357s with them to heaven.
我只希望上帝可以他把警察配У教焯
It's our moment, Allen.
我的r代砼R了 艾
Our moment to step up and be the guys.
我代替他z的r代砼R了
We're at a funeral. Show some respect.        What?
我在葬Y上呢 o他c尊重吧      什N?
You don't think every other detective here
你不X得每一在龅木察
isn't thinking the same thing?
都在想同一件事?
Allen, listen to me. Danson and Highsmith are gone.
艾 我f 丹森和海史密斯已死了
Their desks are empty. Someone has to fill those seats.
他人去桌空 得有人填a他的位
That someone is us, okay? The city's dying for a hero.
那就是我了好不好? ~sF在急缺英雄
Is it?        Yeah.
是?      是的
What about nine million socially-conscious and unified citizens,
那要是九百f有社交意R 有F精神的公民
all just stepping up and doing their part?
都想要代替他的位置怎Nk?
As a little kid, didn't you dress up and play cops and robbers?
小r候 你]有玩^警察抓小偷?
I'll tell you what I did as a little kid.
我告V你我小r候做^什N吧
I went to school and made my bed.
我去上W 整理床
And at age 11, I audited my parents.
十一qr 我查了我父母的~本
And believe me, there were some discrepancies, and I was grounded.
我告V你 事情出了c小差e 我就被他禁足了
What the hell are you?
你是哪淼墓痔グ?
Well, well, well. What do we got here?
看看l砹
Look at these two jamokes, would you?
看看@傻蛋
One shot Jeter and the other shot an office.
一射中了芴 另一在警署_
Have some decorum. We're at a funeral.
嘴巴乾Qc 我在⒓釉岫Y呢
You wanna dance, brolio?
你要跳舞 小?
I will rock your body with big, nasty hooks.
我要用我的巨根爆你菊花
You'll be pissing blood out of your ass.
你後庭流血
That's horrible.
K啊
Why don't you step back, man?
你靠那N近致?
You touch him, I swear to God
你敢碰他 我ι系郯l誓
I'm gonna beat the shit out of you with Allen's head.
我用艾的^把你打得屁股_花
He's not gonna do that. That's hyperbole. But that's a weird example.
他不@N做的 他只是 不^有c怪
You wanna go?        I wanna go!
你想打架?      打就打!
Get him off.        Kick his ass, Martin.
打倒他      扁他 R丁
Yeah. How do you like that?
@尤绾?
Pull his hair!        I love it.
抓他^      我喜g
This hurts so good.
@下可真疼
Very sorry for your loss, ma'am.        What a lovely hat.
哀 女士      多高雅的帽子啊
I love your shoes.
我勰愕男
It's fine, it's fine.        Go, go.
好了好了      ^m ^m
Punish him!
教他!
Oh, man.
哦 有]搞e
Do it. That's how we do it in the hood.
就@ 我就是@幼龅
Punish him.        That's not even a move.
教他      根本就]有@N幼
I'm the winner. I'm the winner, everybody saw it.
我A了 我A了 每人都看到了
What the hell is going on here?
你在搞什N鬼?
Two good men are dead,
好人死
you guys are fighting over who's gonna be the next hotshot?
你就榱苏l⒗^承他的x煌而打架?
Is that what's happening?
是@N回事?
Yes, that's exactly what's happening.
是 就是@N回事
Let me tell you something.
我告V你
Sorry for your loss, Lorraine.        Very sorry.
哀 _琳      哀
Sorry, Lorraine.        Sorry, Lorraine.
哀 _琳      哀 _琳
Hi, I'm Jimmy.
你好 我叫吉米
Too soon?        Why'd you say that?
太早了吧       你致镎f@?
I'll tell you something about those guys.
我告V你 @人
They knew that to become a good cop,
他之所以是好警察
you had to solve cases. Okay?
因樗解Q了很多案子 好不?
Okay, and maybe you start with the Castien robbery.
好 也S你可以目ㄋ沟偈Ц`案_始
Okay? So just watch it.
好不好? 所以注意c
Next time, me, you, library.
下次我跟你在D^打
Not even close.        Come on, guys. Guys, come on.
甭想      戆 夥
You are...        I'm the winner!
你是...      我A了!
I didn't need you to stick up for me, okay?
我不需要你臀出^ 好?
I could've handled that myself.
我可以自己解Q
Hey, don't flatter yourself. It's the partner's code. I had no choice.
e自倭 我是搭nN 我eox
Move.
走_
9:15, let's have a great day, everybody!        Cut the shit!
九c十五 祝大家度^美好的一天      ]嘴
Good morning.
早上好
We've got shots fired. 509 East 10th Street.
有人_了 在西十街509
There are large amounts of cocaine on the scene.
F霭lF大量可卡因
Try to stay out of trouble, boys.
e惹麻┝
There's no chance you'd wanna go on that call, right?
你肯定不去那Y的 ?
No chance. Too busy.
想也e想 太忙了
All right, ladies. Starting to get the picture?
好吧 女生 看到了]?
We're about to lock shit down.
@案子w我搞定了
That's right.        You girls stay here and get your type on.
]e      你女生乖乖呆在@Y吧
Go get them, guys. Lot of energy, lot of focus.
抓住他 夥 能量多多 Ｗ⒍喽
Shut up!
]嘴!
Allen, could I see you in the hallway for a second?
艾 我可以在走廊跟你f拙?
I...I'm super busy right now, Terry.
我...我F在超忙 特Y
No, no, no, I know. This'll be real quick.
不不不 我知道 很快f完
It's about the construction permits you were talking about.
是P於我^的建B工程批准令
The scaffolding violations?        This is our thing, yeah.
非法搭建_手架?      @才是我的案子
So, what do you got?
你查到什N了?
I got this! I'll put one right in your neck.
@! 老c
What are you doing?
你质颤N呢?
Let's go. We're going to that call.
走吧 我去k案
What is this?        Shut up.
你致?      ]嘴
We're going to the car, and we're going after this case.
我_ 我要接k@案子
You're not gonna shoot me.        I won't?
你不向我_的      我不?
No.        I shot Jeter.
不      我向芴亻_^
That was an accident.        Was it?
那是意外      是?
Now move.        Okay.
快走      好吧
Hey.
嘿
Does anybody see this? He's got a gun on me.
看到]有? 他用χ我
I'm being kidnapped.
我被架了
Really, we're in a police station and no one is interested in this?
@Y是警署啊 怎N]人感d趣?
So, then what happened?        What do you think happened?
l生什N了?      你fl生什N了?
I woke up, I took the belt off my neck,
我醒 解_脖子上的ё
and I got in my car, and I got out of there.
然後上去了那Y
Talk about a wild weekend, right?
一狂的L末 ?
I thought I was gonna have to shoot my way out.
我本硪槲乙⒊鋈サ
What are you gonna do, though, you know? Bar mitzvahs.
你要做什N呢? 受戒Y
What the hell is this?
@是什N?
It's my car. It's a Prius.
是我的 普J斯
I feel like we're literally driving around in a vagina.
感X跟在道Y{似的
Detective Hoitz and Gamble are on that 518 on East 10th.
霍探T和甘博警T在西十街518
Negatory, Martin and Fosse, two minutes out.
e想 R丁和佛西 出煞昼了
We'll just see who's there first.
看看l先到
You stay out of our crime scene! You hear me?
x犯罪F鲞hc! 你到]?
Go, go, go!
快 快 快
You feel that, Allen? That tingling in your balls?
感受到了 艾? 蛋蛋是不是d^了?
Big metal butterflies fluttering around in your stomach?
肚子Y面有金俸蝶在煽映岚?
Are you sure you don't have testicular cancer?
你_定你]有前列腺癌?
I got something to get you going.
我知道@可以你d^起
Let's go do some damage!
我去搞c破!
Nope.
不
What the hell is that?
@是什N?
LRB. Little River Band.
小河逢
This music makes me feel like I'm going shopping for a training bra.
@音诽娘了
You know what? We go with no music, okay?
你知道? 我是e音妨 好不好?
Fine.        Say bye.
好      f再
No, no, no, don't say bye...
不不不 不要...
You just signed your own death warrant, Hoitz!
你死定了 霍
Allen, punch that accelerator or I will shoot you in the foot!
艾 你要是不踩加速器我就射你的_!
America!
美fq!
Allen! Allen, hit the brake!
艾 艾 踩x!
Seriously, slow the car down! We're approaching the crime scene!
真的 慢c_ 我快到犯罪F隽
Terry, I'm coming in.
特Y 我砹
You're gonna smash right through the tape! Allen!
你穿^那ё拥 艾!
Dude! What...
老兄! 有]...
That's a lot of cocaine.
好多可卡因啊
Did you yell "America" when you hit the accelerator?
你踩加速器的r候是不是喊道"美fq"?
Nope. No. No.
] ]有
I've never actually put my foot all the way down
我]像@
to the ground with the accelerator like that.
一_踩到底^呢
It got me slightly aroused.
我有c性^了
Here we go.
砹
Way to put your stamp on the crime scene, guys.
等不及要到犯罪F霭 夥
Prius, huh?        Yep, yep.
普J斯?      是的是的
Good mileage?
省油吧?
Outstanding.        Yeah.
好著呢
Did this come with a dental dam?
@Y面是不是有牙科用z布啊?
No.        Get it?
]有      ]有N?
My Suburban shit one of these last night.
昨晚我在一雪佛m上找到@玩意
I didn't know they put tampons on wheels.
我不知道他在子上放l生棉呢
We've had our fun, huh?
我玩得挺_心 是不?
Looks like Scarface sneezed on your car.
就好像疤面煞星朝你上打了嚏
All right, everybody!
好了 各位!
I'm gonna need you all to back up now. We're taking over.
F在你後退 我接手了
"At the crime scene, LOL."
"我在犯罪F 哈哈哈"
Good tweet, good tweet.        Yeah, thanks.
我上脖通知一      xx
America has always been defined by its excess.
美以Ya^剩而出名
The Grand Canyon, professional sports contracts.
大{谷有多N的\T契s
Wendy's Baconator, extra bacon.
氐h堡店有多N的培根
I myself have 18 Lamborghinis
我自己有18vm博基尼
and a Subaru station wagon.
有v斯巴敞篷金
And it's because of this excess that I have flourished.
就是因橘Ya^剩我才能奢侈]霍
I implore you, please, do not stop profiting.
我┣竽 不要停止取利
Live for excess. It's the American way.
^著Ya^剩的日子 @才是美的生活
Hello.
你好
Mr. Ershon? I believe this call's for you.
厄森先生? 您的
Sir David.
我是大l
David. You're not returning my calls,
大l 你]回我
so I'd like you to meet Roger Wesley.
我想你_堋ろf斯利
G'day, mate.        Hey.
你好 夥      你好
Roger and his team are gonna babysit you because I don't trust you,
_芎退的FO督你 因槲也幌嘈拍
because I think you're going to take off.
我知道你_溜
Pamela, this is ridiculous. I'm not going anywhere.
帕米拉 真是荒 我哪Y也不去
David, listen, the Lendl quarterlies come out on the 26th.
大l 著 m道季刊在二十六l行
You have until then to give me my money.
如果你那r候不我X的
I'm not reporting any losses, David.
我就蟾嫖业p失 大l
I have zeroed in on a new investor.
我盯上了一新投Y者
Well, then, you get their money,
那N 你拿走他的X
make it disappear, and then pay us back.
然後它消失 再付o我
Yes, yes, I'll tell him he doesn't need to keep watching me.
好好 我告V他不必盯o我
David!        Okay, sweetheart, bye-bye.
大l!      好了  再
Yeah. She overreacted. She's a woman. So, you're good to go.
她反^度了 女人嘛 所以你可以走了
Heard everything, mate.
我什N都到了 夥
Ladies and gentlemen,
女士先生
guess who gave me the secrets to making my first billion dollars.
猜猜是l告V了我我十|元的秘密?
That man there.
@位先生
Go! Go!
跟上! 跟上!
Side!        Step aside, please.
靠      靠
You don't think I'm a real cop, do you?
你J槲也凰憔察 是?
No, I don't. I've said that directly to your face numerous times.
不 我面γ娓你f了很多次了
I was really honest about that.
我很坦\地δ阏f^了
I'm working on a huge case, all right?
我在理大案子 好不好?
Property owner with seven buildings under construction.
一名下有七施工中房屋的地a商
He hasn't applied for a single scaffolding permit.
他B一_手架批准令都]有
Now, according to Ask Jeeves,
根百度知道
this perp is at the Plaza Hotel speaking right now.
@嫌疑犯正在V鼍频暄葜v
That's your big case? Scaffolding permits?        Yeah.
@是所^的大案子? _手架批准令?      Π
Guess what? You're coming with me.
知道? 你要和我一起
It's a wooden gun.
@是把木
That hurts, man!
很疼啊
I've always got Little River Band loaded up here.
我是有小河F的歌
I've got six disks in here.
我有六P歌碟呢
Claude, meet me outside, at the back of the service entrance.
克洛德 在外面我 在咨台的後面
I'm flying Air Singapore.
我要坐新加坡航空
Hey, Douglas. How's the wife?        She died.
嘿 道格拉斯 你妻子怎?      她死了
Attaboy!
太好了!
I'll be there in two minutes exactly.
煞昼後到
Another thing I hate about you? You always pay in exact change.
有一件很的事 你是付零X
You're just mad because I have a nice change purse.
你只是嫉妒我的零X包很好
Why do you even care?
你管那N多稚?
How can I help it? You know what? You know what's worse?
我怎N能不管? 你知道? 你知道什N更糟?
The way you fart. Even your farts, they're not manly.
你放屁的方式 你B放屁都不像男人
You're being ridiculous.
真是荒
They sound like a baby blowing out the candles on a birthday cake.
起硐裥吹生日T
What?        Like a little...
什N?      像...
You know what bugs me about you?        What?
你知道你有什N人的地方?      什N?
I'm pretty sure you've never voted.
我敢肯定你]投^票
No, I vote. Sports radio, AM 880. Play of the week.
不 我有^ w育台 {l880 本周最佳\T
You're like a child in a leather jacket. That's what you're like.
你就像一穿著皮A克的小孩 你就是像
Get out of the way, man!
e趼 夥!
Wait. Are you David Ershon?
等等 你是大l・厄森?
Yeah, well, it's Sir David Ershon, but I don't bother with the...
是大l・厄森先生 我其也不在意你...
Anyway, little bit of a rush, gentlemen, if you don't mind. Thank you.
其 我在s路 如果你不介意的 xx
Excuse me, but you're under arrest, okay?        What?
Σ黄 你被捕了 好不好?      什N?
You have the right to remain silent. Anything you do or say can be used
你有啾３殖聊 你所f的⒈...
What's the next part?        As a floatation device.
後面是什N?       用作腋≡O
As a floatation device.
用作腋≡O
You know what? That's very funny. I have never Miranda-ed anyone before.
你知道? 挺搞笑的 我]有抓^人呢
Really?        Are you guys for real?
真的?      你诱娓竦?
Am I being punk'd?
我是不是撞到鬼了?
Detective Allen Gamble.
艾・甘博探T
We are in a cocaine-covered car,
我在一v被可卡因覆w的Y
and we are bringing in a perp.
正б幻嫌犯回去
One David Ershon.        175 pounds.
大l・厄森      175磅
Thank you. 175 pounds.        Shut up, man, shut up!
xx 175磅      ]嘴 ]嘴
Martin and Fosse are probably on Studio B
R丁和佛西也S在B室
talking to Shepard Smith right now.
和x伯德・史密斯v呢
We arrest this jerkoff for a scaffolding permit?
我因橐_手架批准令逮捕@混蛋?
Wait, wait, wait, what am I being arrested for?
等等 你槭颤N逮捕我?
For scaffolding permit violation...
`反_手架批准令
I got my insurance card. Somewhere.        Easy, mate.
我有保U卡的 我找找      e激 夥
What the hell? You ran right into us!        Stand over there.
怎N回事? 你撞了我      站在那e
Wood?
木^?
What the...
搞什N...
Couldn't see the car. It's big enough, mate.        What?
看不到我的 虼罅 夥       什N?
Do not let these men take me.
e他ё呶
Hi.
你好
Why's she looking at you like that?
她槭颤N@涌粗我?
That's my car!
那是我的!
Hey, hey, hey! We didn't exchange insurance information!
嘿嘿嘿 我]交Q保U信息呢
Hey! Excuse me!
嘿 到]!
Why did they take our shoes?
他槭颤N拿走我的鞋?
What the hell just happened?        Where's my iPhone?
怎N回事?      我的iPhone呢?
I think we've walked 30 blocks, man.
我X得我走^了三十街^了 夥
I don't get why we can't just call the office
我不知道槭颤N我不能打o警署
and have a squad car come pick us up.
他送v斫游
No. They took our shoes, our guns, and our car.
不 他拿走了我的鞋 我的 有我的
There's no way that's going out on the radio.
我可不能署Y人知道
Look, if we're gonna do this together,
如果我要合作
there's some issues we need to settle, okay?
有些}我必要解Q 好?
I mean, you said I had a weak chin. You said the way I pee is feminine.
我f 你f我下巴不明@ 你f我尿尿像娘
How do you think that makes me feel?
你X得我感受如何?
I mean, that list you have, you put a lot of thought in. It's weird.
我f 你的那清 你考]得挺周到 很奇怪
I hear you.
我到了
Let's clean the slate right now. Fresh start.
我冰前嫌 重新_始吧
All right. Fresh start.
好 重新_始
Maybe we should call ourselves the Febreze Brothers,
也S我叫必m兄弟
'cause it's feeling so fresh right now.
因楦杏X清新舒m
Right?
?
Let's do another fresh start,
我再重新_始一次
'cause I just wanted to punch you in the face.
因槲蚁胱崮愕哪
Fine, fresh start.
好 重新_始
It's the last one.
最後一次
I have to be able to express myself and say things, you know.
我要能虮磉_清楚再和你交 你知道
Okay, folks! Everybody, listen up!        Listen up!
夥 大家都好了!      好了!
Got a high profile kidnapping.
光天化日之下l生了一起架案
David Ershon, wealthy banker, multinational team.
大l・厄森 富有的y行家 有跨F
Maybe a sleeper cell, but it's too early to tell.
劫持者可能早已埋伏在那 但f不准
Hey, Bilbo Baggins. Where are your shoes? 'Cause your feet are black.
小矮人 你的鞋呢 _都黑乎乎的
Who cares? It's not important, okay?
l在乎? @不是重c
Hoitz, Gamble, Captain. Not good.
霍 甘博 ^^找你 情r不妙
Bye, guys.        Bye-bye.
再 夥      再
Come on.
^
Guys, this is Don Beaman, the attorney for Mr. Ershon.
@是唐・比曼 厄森先生的律
Roger Wesley, head of his private security.
_堋ろf斯利 私人保S人
Hey, how are you? You son of a bitch!        Hey, hey, hey!
嘿 你@v人!      淡定淡定!
Hey, Terry! Take it easy!
特Y e激!
That's the guy who took our guns, Captain.
L官 就是他把我的走了
And my shoes!        Wait a minute, wait a minute.
有我的鞋      e激
Did you identify yourselves as police officers?
你表明警察身份了
What is this?
看@是什N
Allen, tell me. Did you?        No, we did not.
艾 告V我 你表明了      ]有
Sorry, gentlemen.
Σ黄 先生
We thought you were abducting Mr. Ershon.
我以槟r在架厄森先生
It's only protocol.
我只是按矩k事
Mr. Ershon has agreed to correct this scaffolding situation.
厄森先生已同意a上_手架事宜
The case is closed.
@事就Y了
I've taken care of all necessary paperwork.
所有必要的面材料已打理好了
And you fellas, at this point, should just be glad that
F在你c幸
Mr. Ershon is not pressing charges for excessive use of force.
厄森先生]有δ^度使用武力提起VA
Thank you, Captain.        You bet.
xx L官      客饬
Australian?
你澳大利的?
Special Forces, right?
特N兵?
Best watch your step, Detective.
你最好o我小心c 探T
There are three things I love in this world.
@世界上有三件|西我最喜g了
Kylie Minogue,
P利・米洛(澳大利女歌手)
small dimples just above a woman's buttocks...
女人的股
Beautiful features.
的_很好看
...and the fear in a man's eye who knows I'm about to hurt him.
和即挨揍的男人眼中的恐
Hey! Shake your dicks. This pissing contest is over.
你蛋疼完了] 正事k完了就走
Come on, man.
算了
All right, look, they returned your shoes.
看 他把鞋子回砹
And they returned your weapons. Here you go, Terry.
你的武器也回砹 o你 特Y
Allen, someone was nice enough to put linseed oil on it,
艾 有人湍悴亮它c麻油
some kind of stain on that, dark walnut or something.
上面粘了似深核桃木的污n
You might wanna think about dropping them a thank you note.
你o他封感x信
Okay.
好了
You're mad at us, huh, Gene?
你在生我的馐前 吉恩
First off, don't call me Gene. I'm your captain.
第一 不要叫我吉恩 我是你的L官
Guys, do you remember the "Be Smart" speech?
你忘了那"W明c"的演v
Sure.        All right.
]忘      那N
Well, what did you do? What'd you do about it?
你是怎N做的 你怎N理的
The opposite. We were not smart, Captain Gene.
好相反 我不C` 吉恩L官
It's just "Captain. "
叫我"L官"就好了
Just "Captain. " It's not "Captain Gene. " I don't have a kiddie show.
就叫"L官" 不是"吉恩L官" 又不是少汗目
That sounds creepy, "Captain Gene. "
"吉恩L官" 著太不o力了
Police mistakenly arrest investment banker, David Ershon.
警方e`抓捕了投Yy行家大l・厄森
Was he the victim of financial profiling?
他是辗治鼋Y果的受害者
Financial profiling? That's crazy.
辗治? 太扯了吧
He broke the law and we arrested him.
明明是他犯了法我才逮捕他
That wasn't a security team. He said, "Don't let these people take me. "
那不是他的保S 他f"e@些人ё呶"
I mean, when you hear hooves, you think horses, not zebras.
你到R蹄二字 想到的肯定是R 而不是羊吧
What about donkeys or deer?
槭颤N不是牛或者H呢?
They have hooves. What about bovine creatures?
它都L蹄子 牛科游锷耨R的?
Were you just thinking to yourself, "Fresh start"?
你是在想 "要有一新_始"?
Yeah.        Yeah. I could see it.
是的      嗯 我看出砹
Listen, why don't we just go over to my place?
要不去我家吧
We'll talk the case down.
我好好@案子
We can have a little dinner. You can meet Sheila.
吃蔚耐聿 你可以JR希拉
Two cops talking down a case while eating food, all right?
我z只是作榫察在吃r候公蘸貌缓?
It's not dinner.        Fine.
不是神R晚餐      好吧
And let me apologize in advance, okay,
我先提前道歉
in case my wife acts like a world-class bitch.
f一我老婆表F得跟h球第一v人一
She's a big old broad, and she likes to wield it.
她又老又肥 得瑟得很
Okay, so I put together a little bio,
我把大l・厄森的人Y料
complete with pictures of Mr. David Ershon.
和照片整理了一下
I used Adobe Premiere. I like to do a little weekend editing.
我用的Adobelw 我喜gL末做c的活
I recently just cut three minutes out of Goodfellas.
我"I亦有道"Y剪了3分的R^
David Ershon is currently the CEO of Ershon Consortium.
大l・厄森目前是厄森F的CEO
Who's that talking?
是l在旁白?
It's the Frontline Narration App. It's only 99 cents.
是一Z音用 只要99美分
Ershon Consortium, current financial investments exceed $70 billion.
厄森F目前的金融投Y超^了700|美元
His largest clients include Schering-Plough and Lendl Global.
他的大客舭括S-P公司和m道公司
Lendl Global has those TV ads where I can't figure out what they do.
m道公司拍了一些不明所以的V告
Yeah, oil, media, health care,
是啊 石油 髅 社保都有涉及
you've probably heard their jingle.
你知道他的影力
Lendl Global, we're in everything
m道公司 我o不在
David Ershon is often found in the company of Judge Scalia...
大l・厄森常在思嘉利的公司出F
Yeah.        ...and the lead singer of Maroon 5.
是啊      有Maroon 5的I唱
I mean, this guy could be connected to drug cartels,
@人可能跟毒集F
black market organ sales, human trafficking, all of it.
黑市器官u和人子有M
How do you get that from anything I just said?
你的Y和我才f的有PS?
Hey, guys! Soup's on.
嘿 砹
What do you mean?
什N意思
Hi.
嗨
Hi.        You must be Terry.
嗨      你肯定是特Y
I'm sorry I've been hiding, honey, but this dinner was tricky.
H鄣 我不躲著你的朋友 晚太折v了
Who are you?        I'm Dr. Sheila Gamble, his wife.
你是l?      我是希拉・甘博 他老婆啊
Come on, seriously. Who is that?        His old lady.
f真的 她是l      他的S婆
Sweetie, it's a workstation.        Got it.
小甜心 我在工作呢      明白
And you come in here, dressed like a hobo, it's distracting.
你衣不蔽w的幼 太人分心了
I know you're working. I'm so sorry.
我知道你在工作 Σ黄
Come on, seriously.        Come on, what?
我f真的      真的什N?
Who is that?
她是l?
That's the old...That's the old ball and chain.
她是老...她是我的
Get over here.
啵一
Not...Not right now.        Okay.
不 @Y不合m      好吧
Look, they're not all first-round picks, okay?
那些都不是考]的重c
Come on, are you gonna tell me who that is?
你到底f不f她是l
Are you really Allen's wife?        I know.
你真的是艾的妻子?      我就知道
People are shocked
他信}公教 我信天主教
because he's Episcopalian and I'm Catholic,
e人都不信我能在一起
but somehow it works.
但事就是@
Are you gonna change?        I already did.
你要Q身衣服?      我Q了啊
It's no big deal. You look really, really nice.
]PS 你看上去漂亮O了
Terry, you don't have to be polite, okay? She looks kind of shitty.
特Y ]必要跟她客 她穿得太Lm了
Don't speak to her like that, Allen.
不S你@诱f她 艾
Look, if I put that in my Cosmo Fashion App,
如果我把你@身打扮放到潮人用Y面
you'd probably get a D-.
你可能不及格
Allen and his apps. He loves them.
艾最喜g_l用程序了
You know he's designed three of his own? One of them...Can I tell him?
他自己O了3用 有一...我能f?
One of them, you can take a picture of anybody's face,
有一程序 你可以拍任何人的正面
and it'll tell you what the back of his head looks like.
它就告V你@人的後X勺是什N拥
Faceback.        Faceback.
叫人人後X勺      人人後X勺
Got some horrible reviews coming out of the gate.
已收到很多F的u了
It's gonna hit.        It's gonna catch.
肯定火的      很吸引眼球
Why are you with Allen?
你槭颤N跟了艾?
I mean, that's not what I meant. I meant, how did you guys meet?
不是那意思 我是f 你z怎NJR的?
It's a really typical "how we met" story, Terry.
@是一典型的邂逅故事 特Y
You're gonna be bored by it.
太乏味了
I was a dancer for the Knicks
r我在尼克斯跳舞
while finishing my residency at Columbia Hospital.
平r是哥比t院的生
Allen came into the ER with poison ivy on his rectum.
艾直c上起了毒疹 送到急救室
Yes.
是的
Needless to say, I fell for him immediately.
不用f 我λ一R情
We immediately spent the next three days at the La Quinta Inn,
我在快捷酒店翻覆雨了3天
and, to be honest, we didn't speak.        Three days
老f 我B都]f一句      整整3天
of not communicating once verbally.
一次都]f^
We had actually, without knowing it,
不知不X中
developed a language of eye flutters and non-verbal gestures.
我W用眼神{情 用身wZ言交流
You know, Terry, it was just this primal connection.
特Y 我之g有一N原始F性的n
After those three days of non-verbal communication
^3天垡獾
and a whole lot of loving,
身w交流
I had to go to a specialist to get my hips realigned.
我的屁股都抽筋了 我不得不去看t生
Similar to operating on a German shepherd
就像o屁股l育不良的德牧羊犬
when they have hip dysplasia.        Very painful.
做手g一      疼死我了
It's funny, it's like a scene from that one movie,
特e有意思 像那部影的情一
always forget the name of it.
我是忘名字
With Meg Ryan.        Yes.
梅格・瑞恩演的      就是
I don't remember a movie where Meg Ryan
我不得梅格・瑞恩在什N影Y
meets a guy with poison ivy up his ass.
邂逅^屁股L的男人
I'll think of it. I'll think of it.        Okay.
我想想 我想想      好
So, what about you, Terry? Do you have a girl?
特Y 你呢 有女朋友]
I did, yeah.
以前有
We were supposed to get married, but she backed out. It's complicated.
我本要Y婚的 但她後硗丝s了 事情比^}s
Terry shot Derek Jeter.
特Y朝德Y克・芴亻_了一
Shut up, Allen. This was before.
]嘴 艾 @是哪子的事了
That's okay.
]PS
She's Got Mail. That's the name of the movie.
影的名字是 "子情"
That's it! Honey!
H鄣
With Tom Hanks?        Right.
姆・h克斯演的?      是的
And Meg Ryan.        Meg Ryan.
有梅格・瑞恩      梅格・瑞恩
He didn't have poison ivy up his ass.
他屁股上可]L
Yes, he did.        Yes, he did. Yeah.
他L了的      他真的L了的
Way up there.
就L那旱
Well, Terry, can't thank you enough for coming by. What a...
特Y 很s幸你能砦壹叶冗^@右...
What a wonderful, lovely evening. Thank you.
一剀懊篮玫囊雇 xx
It was so, so nice meeting you, Terry.
很高dJR你 特Y
It was my pleasure. Thank you.
是我的s幸啊 xx
And remember, all I ask of you is, you don't let him get hurt, Terry.
住 我只有一求 不要他受 特Y
She tells me that every day before I leave.        Yep, I do.
我每天上班前她都要@Nf      必的
I come downstairs and I make him his fresh-cut strawberries,
我下墙o他做r草莓汁
and I say, " Listen, my little sugar balls, whatever you do today,
我f "小 不管你今天多忙"
"you just don't get hurt. "
"都不要受"
Yeah. Every morning.
是啊 每天早上都f
And then I show him my breasts, and I say, " These are waiting for you
接著我o他看我的咪咪 我f "它在等你"
"when you get back home. "        Right.
"等你回家"      就是
You know, Terry, they're not the biggest breasts he's ever seen,
特Y 我的胸部不是他^最大的
but, man, are they perky.        Not by a long shot.
但是它很神      ^不是最大的
And they are firm, and they are yours.        You're a nice lady.
它很酝 它凫赌      你很漂亮
Thank you for coming.
xx你能
Detectives Hoitz and Gamble? Detectives Hoitz and Gamble? Over.
霍和甘博探T? 霍和甘博探T? 完
Go for Hoitz.
霍在
We found your red Prius.        Great.
我找到你的普J斯了      太好了
It was trying to vote for Ralph Nader.
它正打算槔夫・鹊(活蛹)投票
Come on.        Okay, sugar balls, listen up.
得了吧      小 著
There's gonna be fingerprints on that car.
上肯定有指y
Tomorrow, we're gonna run those fingerprints through the system.
明天我去提取指y 放M系yz索
And if we get a hit,
一旦得到匹配Y果
this case is gonna heat up faster than a junkie's spoon.
案子M展肯定萑缙浦
You do one thing when you wake up tomorrow, bring it.
明天早上你起床後就做一件事 上子
Okay.        Thank you, Sheila.
好的      xx 希拉
He'll bring it.
他上子的
Good night!        Good night.
晚安      晚安
Thank you, Sheila.
xx你 希拉
Bye, Terry!        Bye, Sheila! I'll never forget tonight.
再 特Y      再 希拉 我不忘今晚
Bye, Terry!        All right, Allen, whatever. Go inside.
再 特Y      行了 艾 回去吧
Bye, Sheila!
再 希拉
Night!        See you...See you, Terry!
晚安      再...再 特Y
I don't know if he heard me. Bye, Terry!
不知道他] 再 特Y
Bye, Sheila!
再 希拉
Well, here she is. They left her under an overpass for the night.
在@了 他把它扔在一座天蛳
You find anything?
有什NlF
Yeah. We found a lot of stuff.
很多lF
From bodily fluid and hair samples,
有w液啊毛啊什N的
we determined that a bunch of old, homeless dudes
我相信有一o家可w的老流浪h
had an orgy in the car.
在Y_^狂g晚
Oh, God.        Yeah.
天哪      哀吧
You know what that's called when they do that in there?
你知道他把@N狂g叫什N
That's called a soup kitchen.
流N房
It's pretty rough stuff.
vy差啊
Not long after that, a mama raccoon came along
不多久 一b母浣熊到Y
and gave birth on the floor.
生了仔
Placenta blew out all over the back window there.
胎P都到後窗上了
Yeah, and then to top it all off, some joker comes along
後 有小鬼到Y的{座上
takes himself a nifty little dump in the driver's seat.
拉了一坨有技g含量的屎
I think he knew you guys were cops,
我猜他知道你是警察
because this is what I would call a spite shit.
因槲野阉的便便叫做蓄意褪
You were able to determine all of that
光通^毛和w液颖
from the hair and fluid samples?        Oh, yeah.
你就能推y@N多情?      然了
What about fingerprints? You find any fingerprints?
指y呢 你lF指y了
Nope, couldn't get a one.        Found a cell phone.
]有 什N指y都]有      找到一部手C
Yeah, that's mine.
是我的
Any signs of a struggle or spent shells?
有]有暝或搏Y的痕E?
No. Believe me, everybody that was in on this orgy was more than willing.
]有 砜g的都是自的
In fact, they even left you a note here.
其他o你留了便l
"Thanks for the F-shack. Love, Dirty Mike and the boys. "
"xx你的小づ 勰 t⒏绾托值"
Here's something we found.
@是在Y找到的
We found about a dozen unscratched lottery tickets.
我找到一打]刮^的彩票
No fingerprints or nothing. Check that out.
]有指y神R的 你看看
Yeah, it's a real shame, you know.
太z憾了
I got myself a Prius. It's a hell of a machine.
我有台普J斯 F在成破~F了
It's my first brand-new car. I've never owned a new car.
@是我第一v新 我以前]I^新
Found a deer vagina.
lF一^鹿的道
What?        Thought it was human lips at first.
什N?      _始以槭侨说淖齑
Then we took a closer look. It was definitely a deer vagina.
我又仔看了看 ^κ锹沟年道
Not even a free ticket.
B"再硪"都]有
What are we gonna do?
我怎Nk?
We got no fingerprints, a bunch of losing lottery tickets.
指y]提取到 拿了一堆]用的彩票
Look at this, there's a two-minute phone call made after we were jumped.
你看 我被拽下後有人打了2分的
They used your phone?        They ghost dialed.
用你手C打的?      秘密艽虻
Someone probably sat on it.
可能有人在那^O
It could have recorded some of
厄森被抓r
their conversation when Ershon got grabbed.
他的部分可能被下砹
We gotta hear the other side of that call.
我必{查l接到了那
Nope, no, it's nothing.
不 ]必要
Nothing?        It's nothing.
]必要?      ]必要
It's the only lead we have.        It's nothing.
@是唯一的索      真]必要
Why did you just get super jumpy?
你@N激致
What?
怎N了?
It's an ex-girlfriend, okay?
是我前女友
What's the matter? What happened with you guys?
怎N了 你z怎N回事
She was just a bit of a handful, that's it.
]什N 哥不想跟她有半毛X的PS
Allen, it's the only lead we have.
艾 @是我唯一的索
We either go with this or we walk away from this case right now.
要N查下去 要N撒手不管
Fine. Let's go see her.
好吧 去找她
Hello, Christinith.
你好啊 克斯汀妮斯
Hello, Allen.
你好 艾
That's my partner, Terry.        Hi, Telly.
@是我同事 特Y      你好 特R
Holy shit. Dude.        Just relax, relax.
鬼了我      eo 放
I waited for you in Tower Records for four hours.
我在高塔音像店等了你4小r
That was 13 years ago.
那是13年前的事了
Arnold Palmer alert. Arnold Palmer alert.
阿Z・旁姆砝 阿Z・旁姆砝
Who wants some Arnie Palmies?
l要喝家{u的料?
Sweetie, this one has the vodky, right here.
H鄣 @杯有伏特加加哦 @杯
Hal, just place it down, please.        All righty.
放桌上就好了       好滴
Okay.
放好了啦
I did things in bed with you that I haven't done with anyone since.
我跟你合w的姿 都]有跟e人L^
No.
真的]有
Christinith, your husband, it's awkward.
克斯汀妮斯 你老公在 ef了
Oh, no, he knows all of this.
]事 他全知道
You're a lucky dog.        It's true.
你太幸\了      就是
Christine, this is a lovely house.
克斯汀 你家很漂亮
It's Christinith. Are you stupid, or are you deaf?
我叫克斯汀妮斯 你是傻子是@子?
Christinith, you idiot!
克斯汀妮斯 蠢i!
You come to our house, you get my wife's name right!
到我家 就得把我老婆的名字叫α!
What?        Christinith!
什N?      克斯汀妮斯!
Look, we really appreciate the hospitality.
你如此好客 我表示很感
We'd just love to get the message off your cell phone.
我想你的音
We believe it might give us information regarding a kidnapping.
它很有可能PS到一起架案
Okay. Why don't you come to the kitchen, and I will let you listen to it
好啊 我去N房吧 我把它放o你
and everyone else stay here.
e人都不S
Okay, sweetie.        Come on.
]} H鄣      戆
There's my phone.        Great, thank you for...
在那      太好了 xx...
I hate you, you son of a bitch!
我恨你 你@v人!
You're so strong.        I'm stronger than you will ever know!
你力庹娲      我比你想像的力飧大!
I hate you! I hate you!
我恨你 我恨你
You're so adorable. Look at your face. Look at your face.
你太可哿 看你@蛋 看你@蛋
You go, "I wuv you. " Say it. "I wuv you, Cwistinith. "
f "我耐你" 快f "我耐你 克斯妮斯"
You probably think because of the beard that I'm really hairy.
你可能X得因槲议L了j腮E 所以汗毛很重
But I'm not.
其我]有啦
Shaved.
我刮^的
Allen!        He's fine.
艾!      他]事的
Question.
你一}
What would you rather be,
你想哪N游
a bear or a dog?
熊是狗?
I don't care.        I wanna be
o所^      我想
a bear dog. Half dog, half bear.
熊狗 一半狗 一半熊那N
'Cause that way, I could live in the house
因樾芄芳瓤梢援物住在家Y
but I still get to make a doodie out in the woods.
又能蛉バ淞掷锢屎
Allen!
艾!
Allen! Allen!
艾! 艾!
This is police evidence. Terry! Let's go!        Hey!
@是警方C 特Y 跑啊!      嘿!
You get back here and you make love to my wife!
你得回砀我老婆合w!
Allen! Allen!
艾! 艾!
I don't get it, man. I just do not get it.
我想不通 我在想不通
I mean, that girl Christinith was seriously hot.
克斯汀妮斯身材超辣的
Your wife is crazy hot.
你老婆也人鼻血
I mean, even that Brazilian security chick,
即使旁有巴西人妖
she threw you a "Do me" vibe.
她是暗示你"上我吧"
What is it with you and hot ladies?
你怎N那N吸引辣妹?
First off, my wife is cute, but she's not hot.
首先 我老婆是可 不是火辣
Dude, you're insane. Your wife is scalding hot.
你X子b{糊了 你老婆那N性感
You wanna listen to this message or not?        Yeah, whatever.
你到底不音?      吧
You have one job, mate.
你要去k一件事
Find a sucker to invest with you
找可zx和你共同投Y
so you can pay my boss back the money you lost.
@幽憔湍馨彦Xo我老了
And I don't care who.
我不在乎你找l
Right. I actually think I found a sucker...
α 我想起砦疫@有可zx
He's talking to Ershon. ...to invest $32 billion.
他厄森...投Y320|美元
Who's got $32 billion to rob?
l傻逼兮兮地拿320|人啊
Once I get the money, I'll falsify the records
只要我拿到X 我纂改
to show their massive losses and then repay your employer.
告V他p失K重 再o你的T工付工Y
Now, since you're following me, I need to go to 2300 Park Avenue,
既然你跟著我 我F在就去公@大道2300
and after that...
接著...
I told you it wasn't a security team.
我就f他不是保安
He was being abducted.        Obviously, but what kind...Holy...
他被架了      明@的事 但槭颤N......
Nobody leaves our house without making love to my wife!
M了我家T 必跟我老婆合w!
Is that him?        Yeah!
是他?      是啊
Oh, my God, they came out of nowhere!
他哪好俺淼?
Holy shit!        They chased us 20 miles.
鬼!      他追了我20英里
You come back here! You get back here!        Allen!
回 o我回!      艾!
2300 Park Avenue. It's the offices of the lottery.
公@大道2300 是彩票公司
Holy shit, the lottery tickets we found.
死 就是我找到的那些彩票
Ershon is using the lottery money to cover his losses.
厄森通^l售彩票a他的p失
$32 billion. That's the state's money.
320| 一州的收入啊
Well, what do we tell Mauch? A guy lost some money.
我怎N跟毛奇交代? 有人X了
We have a scratchy cell phone message and an address.
我只有一l粗略的Z音信息和一地址
It's still half a case.
半案子都不算
There's gotta be some sort of paper trail.
肯定有面
If we can find that, if we can track it,
要是能找到 我可以跟
then we can go to Mauch.
然後告V毛奇@事
So, I did some more research on Ershon's accounting firm,
我{查了厄森的公司
and I found some pretty interesting stuff.
lF一些有意思的事
It turns out that Gretchel and Dawson has...
G-D公司...
Hold on, I'm up.
等等 到我了
I gave my love to Erin
我把郢Io了厄琳
She promised to be true
她答等我
I went to war to come back
我錾匣
And find five British soldiers
已有5英士兵
Had their way with her
和她有^偾
It was consensual
他互相吸引
Done?
唱完了?
Gretchel and Dawson Accounting Firm in Fair Lawn, New Jersey
G-D公司在新晌髦莸馁M良
has only one client, David Ershon.
只有一客 大l・厄森
Pretty rinky-dink operation for a guy like that.
@N手法λ碚f太老套了
Looks like we're going to Jersey to visit an accounting firm.
貌似我去新晌靼菰L一下公司
That's a shitty day.
累死人的一天
And all their fathers were hanged
他的父H都被吊死
And the children all got pink eye
所有的孩子哭t了p眼
While their Harry Potter books were burned
哈利波特全集GM火坑
Do you have fun singing those songs? They're really depressing.
唱@些歌很有意思? 太阂至
I do. They're full of rich history.
有意思啊 它包含了深刻的v史
Damn it, I'm late. I was supposed to go meet my lady.
靠 我t到了 去我女朋友的
I thought you said you guys split up.
你不是分手了
Let's just keep our thing about work, okay?
我z之g只工作行
All right. Goodbye, buddy.
好的 再 兄弟
Hey, get off me, man.
e碰我
What the hell are you doing?
你在致锬
I'm dancing, Terry. What the hell are you doing here?
跳舞啊 特Y 你在@致
I love you, Francine.
我勰 弗朗辛
If you were with me,
要是你]和我分手
you wouldn't be here in this strip club, shaking it for dollar bills!
你也不用榱隋X在@跳衣舞啊
This is a ballet studio, Terry. Okay? These poles are horizontal.
@是芭蕾排室 特Y @Y的管是水平的
He loves you very much, Francine.
他很勰 弗朗辛
Who is this guy?        What are you doing here, Allen?
他是l      你在@致 艾?
It's the code. I'm your partner.
我是同事嘛
I'm here to support a friend and a work colleague.
我硗ξ业呐笥鸭婀ぷ麾钒榈
Francine, is this guy bothering you?
弗朗辛 @人在}_你
Who's this, your new boyfriend? Great. You got a new boyfriend.
他是l 你的新男友? 太好了 你有新男友了
He is my dance partner, Terry. Okay?
他是我的舞伴 特Y
I know that this is a big surprise,
我知道@δ碚f是@喜
but there are other things in the world besides being a cop. Okay?
但是除了警察 世界上有很多e的事可做
Now, if you will excuse me, I'm gonna dance.
如果你]e的事的 我要跳舞了
What, you don't think I can do this shit?
怎N 你X得我不@玩意N
That was surprisingly good, Terry.
太出乎意料了 特Y
I love you, Francine.        You don't know what love is.
我勰 弗朗辛      你不懂什N叫
He loves you very much, Francine!
他很勰 弗朗辛!
I heard it when he said it. Thank you.
他f我得 xx你
You know what you're doing to me? You're killing me inside.
你看你怎Nξ业? 你森森地割裂了我的心
And don't eyeball me, man!
e瞪我 死人!
You're running around with this crack-dealing drug addict?
你就跟@N磕~的a君子眉硌廴?
Terry!
特Y!
He does not approve of your behavior!
他δ愕男楹苁望!
Can you please go?
你可以走了
And you, too, creepy guy standing in the door?
你也是 站T口那神病!
Let's go, Allen.
走吧 艾
I think we all experienced our own ballet today.
我今天都跳了一鲎约旱陌爬
The ballet of emotion and feelings.
含情w的芭蕾
You're kind of making things worse.
你是砩匡Lc火的
You okay?        Yeah, I'm fine.
]事吧?      ]事
Hey, I didn't know you could dance.
我不知道你居然跳舞
We used to do those dance moves to make fun of guys when we were kids,
我小r候W的舞步 去取笑e人
show them how queer they were, okay?
o他看@些舞步是多可笑
You learned to dance like that sarcastically?        Yeah, I guess.
你W跳舞是榱酥S刺e人啊?      我想是的
Stay out of my personal life, okay? The kid flies private.
e胶臀业乃饺松活行? 小孩的心思你不懂
Stay focused on the case, man. I'll see you in Jersey tomorrow.
Ｗ⑦@案子吧 明天新晌饕
All right, Terry.
好吧 特Y
Hey, that was liberating for me. I don't know how it felt for you.
我X得很然 不知道你怎N想
Here, check this out. Article from six months ago.
看@ 6月以前的文章
Talking about how the lottery is looking
v了彩票I
to invest their $30-billion fund more aggressively.
投Y300|美元的行檫^於激M
So he's dealing drugs?
所以他在毒?
No, it's not drugs. This isn't Miami Vice.
跟毒]PS 我不是在拍"~阿密L"
Look, I'm sorry. I just...
Σ黄 我...
I am in a bit of a state today. Sheila and I got into it last night.
我今天情w不好 希拉和我昨晚[矛盾了
What happened?
怎N了
She was interested in taking this class at The Learning Annex, right?
她想去M修CW一Tn
Called "The Art of Oral Sex"?
叫"口交的g"
You know, we just don't have it in the budget right now.
我目前]有足虻念A算
It's always about her.
她是只考]自己
Yeah, that's...That's messed up.
是啊...是不
Hey, I got you a gift.
我o你淞艘环荻Y物
I just saw something, and I thought of you,
我看它就想到你了
and so, I don't want it to be weird.
我不想搞得很奇怪
I just wanted to be nice.
只是表示友好哈
Of course it's weird.
然很奇怪了
It's a grown man giving another man a present.
一成年男人o另一男人送Y物
There you go. Open it up.
o你 打_看看
It's okay, you're welcome.
]事的 不用x
I like to do things like that.
我喜g送人Y物
Take a look what it says.
看它f的什N
Female Body Inspector.
女性身wz查官
You know, because we're both in law enforcement.
我都凫谭ㄏ到y
We both like women.
都喜g女人
But I got a weird sense of humor. I'm a sick puppy.
但我的幽默感很奇怪 病B的幽默
I can't look at it. It makes me laugh so hard.
我不能看它 看一眼就要笑死^去
Me, too.
我也是
Real nice. You know, it's all class.
做得好 很有Y貌
Okay.        Don't do that shit any more.
好      e再磉@套了
Yeah, believe me, I won't.
相信我 不了
Do you understand what's so funny about it, though?
你明白它槭颤N搞笑
'Cause it's the FBI, right? It has the same logo, the same shield.
因樗著FBI 字母一 苏I也一
And at first glance, you're like, it's just a mug that says "FBI."
第一眼看上去 它只是一了"FBI"的R克杯
But then at second glance, you're like, "Female Body Inspector"?
但你再看一眼 "女性身wz查官"?
Get out of town. This is outrageous...
太扯了 @都想得出...
Shut up!
]嘴!
I'm gonna climb over that anger wall of yours
有一天 我越^你的怒火
one of these days,
直_你的刃
and it's gonna be glorious.
那⑹俏业墓s
Shouldn't we tell Mauch that we're going to check this place out?
我是不是告V毛奇 我在查@地方?
For what? We're just going to check it out.
槭颤N? 我只是{查一下
I know, but it's procedure.
我知道 但@是程序嘛
Terry answers to no one.
特Y表示沉默
I do what I do.
我致致
What accounting firm is closed at 11:00 a. m. On a Tuesday?
哪家公司在L二上午11cPT啊?
This is a shithole.
@就是空
I love bombs.
我喜g爆破
I can't hear! I can't hear!
我不了! 我不了!
There's blood blisters on my hands!
我手上起水泡了!
Oh, my God!
~滴神!
How do they walk away in movies without flinching
槭颤N影Y的人]有被炸w
when it explodes behind them?
能安然o恙地路^呢?
There's no way! I call bullshit on that!
不可能! 影神R的都是浮!
When they flew the Millennium Falcon outside of the Death Star,
他乘坐千年wx死亡之星r
and it was followed by the explosion, that was bullshit!
死亡之星就l生了大爆炸 全是鬼扯!
Don't you dare badmouth Star Wars! That was all accurate!
不S你f星球大鸬脑! 演的都是真的!
I need an MRI.
我要做核磁共振
I need an MRI! I've got soft tissue damage.
我要做核磁共振! 我M受了
There's no way I don't have soft tissue damage.
我的M^κ了
Please stop.
消停一下吧
I just wanna go somewhere and breastfeed right now!
我想蜷s在女人的蜒Y喝奶!
Fire Department said it was a gas leak,
消防部J槭翘烊漏
but no way. That was timed.
但不可能 @是定r炸
They didn't wanna kill us, but they wanted to scare us.
他不想⑽ 他要我害怕
Yeah, well, they succeeded, okay?
是啊 他成功了
I'm tired of this. All right?
我累了 行了吧?
I'm tired of explosions and people pointing guns at me.
我不想再v爆炸或被人用指著^了
I wanna go back to my desk.
我想坐回k公桌跟前
Guess what? Life gets loud sometimes and messes with your ears.
你知道? 生活有r就是@诱鸲欲@
You can't escape it by hiding at your desk for your whole life.
你不能一子都躲在k公桌後面
You know what? Yes, you can. I've done it for years, okay?
槭颤N不可以? 我已躲了很多年了
There's no explosions at my desk.
k公室Y就]有爆炸
There's no explosions at my home with my plain wife, in my plain house.
家Y有豪宅善 但]有爆炸
What are you afraid of, man?
你在害怕什N?
I'm your partner. You can tell me. What the hell are you hiding from?
我是你的搭n 你可以告V我 你在害怕什N?
I was a sophomore in college.
我那r大二
The university I went to decided they needed to raise tuition.
我x的大WQ定增加WM
A classmate of mine, Brenda,
我一同W 布m_
in an effort to raise money and stay in school,
榱嘶IX交WM
came up with a nifty plan
想到了一好c子
where she thought she'd date guys and charge them money.
就是跟男生s 他要X
I go on dates all the time,
我Sr都有s
with a whole bunch of, you know, boys and stuff.
跟不同的男人
And I kind of need somebody to help me out,
我需要人兔
like, you know, my partner in crime.
就是找搭n臀烤救
Yeah, I could make a schedule.
嗯 我可以安排
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what I was thinking.
我也是@N想的
Provide transportation services.        Yeah, yeah.
提供接送服帐颤N的
It's gonna be a good time.        Thanks so much for asking me.
聊天很愉快      感x你碚椅
She said she needed my help to make sure that the dates went okay
她f她要我兔 _保s利
and that the guys paid her. She said she'd give me a percentage.
男人付o她X 她答o我分t
Oh, my God. You were a pimp.        What? God, no.
天啊 你是皮l客      什N?  不是
No, I was just trying to help a friend.
我只是想团笥
We started making a lot of money.
我_始炅撕芏噱X
And wouldn't you know it, some of Brenda's girlfriends
]想到的是 布m_的朋友
decided they wanted to be a part of it.
也想加入@活
Pretty soon, there were about 14 ladies that I was protecting
]^多久 我保o的女孩子有14之多
while they gave me money.
她都o我分t
That's called a stable of whores.
你B了一C妓女
We decided I shouldn't use my real name.
我Q定o我Q名字
So we came up with the name "Gator. "
於是我起了"w特"@名
I'm telling you, you were a pimp.
你^κ瞧l客
No! Are you even listening to the story?
不是! 你有]有我f?
Anyway, one day, I wake up and I look in the mirror,
之 有一天我醒 看著R子Y的自己
and I don't like what I see.
lF我自己@副面孔
I mean, I had gotten out of control, and I didn't even realize it.
我已o法掌控局面 而我都]有意R到
You can't have a conscience in the pimp game.
在皮l客那行]有良心可言
One night, two of my favorite girls,
一天晚上 我最喜g的女孩
Candy and Jolene, said, "We gotta take you in,"
P蒂和卓琳f "加入我吧"
and they dropped me off at the emergency room.
接著她把我G在了急救室
That's where I met Sheila. I was a mess.
我就在那遇了希拉 那r我很狼N
I made a promise to myself and to her
我o自己和她SZ
that I would never get out of control again.
再也不能人生失控
So, as soon as I graduated from college,
所以 我一I
I became an accountant for the police department.
就做了警察局的
The most stable job I could think of.
我能想到的最定的工作
An accountant for law and order.
管社治安的
I just don't wanna ever feel out of control like that ever again.
我再也不想w被生活操v的日子了
Don't worry. I got your back.
e心 哥支持你
Now I say we go get in Ershon's grill and see if he cracks.
我去找厄森 看他什N反吧
I'm tired of all this tippy-toeing around.        Okay.
我不想再b手b_地查案了      好
You can either walk the plank or take your panties off.
要N哪景迳献哌^去 要N子
The choice is yours.
你x一
I want to take my panties off.
我x子
You've made a wise choice, you have.
真明
Mr. Ershon, Detective Gamble
厄森先生 甘博探T
and the officer who shot Derek Jeter are here.
和舻卵Y克・芴氐哪侨砹
Gentlemen, please.
M 先生
Remember us, hotshot?        Of course I do. Please, sit.
得我 哥?      然得 坐
There she blows.
看她爆炸了
Two of those Russian waters, please. No lime wedges, just cucumber.
杀伏特加 不要青 只要酸S瓜
Guess where we just came from? An explosion at your accounting office.
猜我哪? 你的公司爆炸了
Yes, that awful gas leak.
是啊 死的天然漏
Gas leak?
天然漏?
The only gas leak is the one coming out of your mouth right now.
你口臭漏差不多
I just thank God no one was hurt or injured in a bad way.
我只能感x上天]人受重
I absolutely abhor death.
我憎恨死亡
Hey, Andrew Lloyd Webber. The jig is up, okay?
得了吧 耶d eb了
We know that wasn't your security team that grabbed you.
我知道抓你的人K非你的保安
And we know you're targeting a big fish to cover losses.
也知道你想引大~上^ap失
You talk or I beat you so it don't show no bruises.
你再胡f 我就打得你鼻青[
God, this water is good. Terry,
@杯水太好喝了 特Y
have you tried the water?        Shut up Allen
你喝了?      ]嘴 艾
I assure you I have no idea what you're talking about
我向你保C 我完全不知道你在f什N
I understand there was a bit of a mix-up
我知道_手架@子事
with the whole scaffolding business.
有一c混y
The cucumber accents the water in such a way that...
@KS瓜@瓶水更加...
Perhaps by way of apology,
榱吮硎疚业那敢
I can offer you my personal courtside seats
我可以送你尼克斯比的前排座位
for the Knicks game, with access to the Ambassador Club.
有大使俱凡康耐ㄐ凶C
Come on, Knicks! Come on!
加油 尼克斯 加油
I got Knicks' fever and it's catching!
我δ峥怂沟目 是很有感染力的
Hey. This feels weird sitting here. It feels like it's a bribe.
嘿 我X得坐到@Y很奇怪 感X像是VT
It is a bribe. Son-of-a-bitch, I saw courtside and I went blind.
是VT 狗仔子 我看到前銎 就]多想了
come on
走吧
call me
打o我
Excuse me.        That was a trick.
抱歉      你耍得什N把
No more
e再玩了
Gentlemen, you have a choice. Mamma Mia or Jersey Boys.
先生 你要x 咪呀是晌髂泻
Fantastic! You're so unbelievable!
太棒了 y以置信
Damn it. He did it again.
死 他又耍了@招
Excuse me.        No more tickets.
不好意思      不要再o票了
Mr. Ershon, I tried to keep them in the waiting room.
厄森先生 我^他在休息室等
That's okay, Susan. Two Glacier waters with Mediterranean limes.
]事 K珊 杀冰川V泉水 加地中海青
No, no, no. No more water. We're not here for that.
不 不 不用 不用水 我不是砗人的
No, I was very much looking forward to having a water.
不 我倒是很想要杯水的
How great is Jersey Boys?        It's not great. It's fantastic!
晌髂泻⒑馨舭?      不是棒 太美妙^了
You totally undersold it. The pageantry, the costumes.
你^vu了 那邀的鼍 服b
Wow, what a musical.
哇哦 正翻了的音
Hey. Get over here.
嘿 ^
What's wrong with you?        What?
你怎N回事?      什N?
That's not what we're here for.
我磉@Y不是聊@的
We're gonna do good cop, bad cop. Okay?
我沓白 黑 好?
It's the oldest game in the book for a reason, it works.
既然是中d中最古老的方法 肯定有用
I come strong, then you come in.
我碛驳 然後你再⑴cM
You got it?        Yeah.
明白?      明白
I come strong, then you come in.        Right. Got it.
我碛驳 然後你⑴cM       明白
Now you listen to me, you piece of shit.
你o我著 你sN
It's just you and me, and I'm gonna rip you apart!
就我z的事 我要把你撕粉碎
How did you cover your losses up?
你是怎N掩w你的p失的?
What drug cartel are you working with now?
你槟毒品巨^u命?
Okay, I'll talk to you, you're reasonable!        No, no, look at me!
好吧 我要和你f 你比^理智      不 看著我
You wanna talk to me? You wanna talk to me?
你想和我f? 你想和我f?
Allen, what are you doing? What are you doing? Allen!
艾 你在? 你在? 艾
I'm gonna make you eat a plate of human shit!
我你吃屎
Get away from me!
o我L_
Where is he?
他在哪?
Look, I'm really sorry about that.
著 我真的很抱歉
I saw how aggressive you were being, and I thought,
我看到你那N有攻粜 我想
"Wow, I gotta go even bigger than that,
"哇 我要做得更狠才行
"since we're doing bad cop, bad cop. "
"因槲在唱黑 黑"
What? No, I said,
什N? 不是 我是f
"Good cop, bad cop. " I'm the bad cop, you're the good cop.
"白 黑" 我是黑 你是白
Okay, then there it is.
好吧 事情都@恿
That's it. I thought you said, "Bad cop, bad cop. "
算了 我以槟阏f黑 黑
Well, while you were going crazy, look what I snagged from his desk.
好吧 你l那 看看我乃桌上拿到什N
Think it's his phone sheet.        Nice.
我想@是他的清      不e
Seven calls to the lottery office.
七打o彩票k公室的
That could be the evidence we need for Mauch.
@可能是我破毛奇案的C
Get back. Colombian drug lords.        Where are you getting that from?
退後 哥比毒n      你哪陌阉招淼?
Jeesus
老天
Can you imagine where you'd be in your career if you hadn't shot Jeter?
如果你]有打芴 你的事I不wSv_?
We call this in, right?
我惹淼 Π?
Looks like we got all the evidence we need.
看砦已拿到所有C了
I'm sorry, my butterfly.
抱歉 我的小蝴蝶
We'll load them up, send them back to go.
我把他b上 把他送回去
Holy shit.        What?
我靠      什N?
What do you mean, what? Where are we?
你什N意思? 什N? 我在哪?
We're in the high desert.
我在沙漠
They took my shoes again, man! What the hell is it with taking shoes?
他又拿走我的鞋子 他的拿我鞋?
They took your wooden gun?        Yeah.
他拿走了你的木?      是的
Hello?        Hello, Gene? I mean, Captain.
喂?      喂 吉恩? 我是f L官
Captain, it's Allen Gamble.
L官 我是艾・甘博
Yeah, yeah. Where are you? What's going on?
是 是 你在哪? l生什N事了?
Captain, it's a long story, but I'm just gonna cut to the chase.
L官 @f碓L了 但是我L短f
We are in Las Vegas, all right?
我在拉斯S加斯 好?
We were kidnapped,
我被架了
put on a freight train, and shipped out here.
被放在一v\火 然後\到@了
Let me just stop you right there. Don't bullshit me.
你就o我f到@ eo我扯蛋
Captain, I am being straight with you.
L官 我就和不你@子了
Look, we think something's going on, okay?
著 我J橛惺掳l生 好?
We think Ershon is targeting the lottery to cover his losses.
我J槎蛏想通^彩票硌谏w他的p失
Wait. How many times did I explicitly say to you, "Lay off Ershon"?
慢著 我明白地告V^你状 "e查厄森"?
Terry, Captain wants to know
特Y L官想知道
how many times has he asked us to lay off of Ershon.
他告V^我状e查厄森了
Twice.
纱
Twice. Terry says twice. I agree.
纱 特Yf纱 我同意
I'm hanging up. I'm done.
我要炝 我o可f
I gotta tell you, I started getting a hand for that,
我跟你f 我手一摸到牌
a taste for that Pai Gow.
牌九的感X立R砹
Martin and Fosse, super cops, in three, two...
R丁和佛西 超警察 三 二
So, we busted that junkie. Got back 74 thou in diamonds. 74 thou.
我暴打那垃圾 拿回了7f4的石 7f4呀
Solved the Castien case.
破了卡斯蒂的案子
$74,000? That's all they took?
7f4? 你就拿回@些?
There's millions of dollars of diamonds in that place.
那Y有上百f的石
How about this, Gamble? How about you shut your face?
@影 甘博? 你]上你的臭嘴行?
All right? Just shut it.
好? ]嘴
Hoitz, Gamble, Captain's looking for you.
霍 甘博 L官找你
I know it's off the subject, but is Kevlar copyrighted?
我知道跑}了 但是P夫拉有版?
Captain?        Yeah.
L官?      是
Is it a bad time?        No, come on. Come on.
我淼牟皇r候?      不 M M
Not me, right?        Yeah, and you.
我不用 ?      是 有你
Fellows, I'm sure you're familiar
夥 我想你一定JR
with the venerable DA Radford.
受人尊敬的拉德福z查官
He wanted to come down and pay us a visit.
他屈尊戆菰L我
Hello, gentlemen.
你好 先生
Hello, sir.        Hey.
你好 先生       嘿
You know, I was talking to Gene here.        He prefers "Captain. "
我在和吉恩      他比^喜gL官@Q呼
Yes, I was talking to Gene here, and, you know, it's funny.
是 我在和吉恩 你知道 有意思的
I don't know what you two have been up to,
我不知道你捅了什Nt子
but I've been getting calls from people I don't ever get calls from.
但我一直接到一些奈创螂o我的人的
In 40 years of enforcing the law, I've learned one thing.
我呆在谭ú块T40年 我W到了一|西
When that happens, stop.
@N事l生的r候 就停手吧
Gene, how's the family?        Good, good, Louis, thanks for asking.
吉恩 你家人怎N?      很好 xx你P心
My son's bisexual, so...        Tremendous.
我鹤邮请p性 所以...      很棒啊
Gentlemen, do we understand each other?
先生 我t解p方的立隽?
Cut the crap!        Will do.
e再多管f事      的
Guy never comes down here.
一]有磉^@的人
Twenty years, I think I've seen that guy in this building one time.
二十年 我想我只在@大茄Y^他一次
He's a heavyweight cat, that guy.        He was sitting right here.
他是重要人物 那人      他就坐在@
Yeah. I think you missed the point. Anyway, look.
是的 我想重c不是@ 不管怎N 著
Blue and white found your firearms down by the Hudson River.
巡警在哈德d河下游找到你的
Here you go, Terry.
o你 特Y
You know what?
@影?
I'm gonna hang on to the wooden gun.
@把木我扣下了
To give me back my real gun?        No.
把真o我?      不
'Cause I'm gonna give you this.
因槲乙o你@
It's a rape whistle. You blow that if you run into any trouble
是把哨子 你碰上麻 就吹@
and someone with an actual gun will come and help you out.
有真的人^湍
We were abducted, Captain! This shit is real!
我被劫持了 L官 @是真的
Ershon's dirty. He's targeting the lottery!
厄森有} 他的目耸遣势
Next, I want you guys to hand in
接下 我要你
all the evidence you think you have to the SEC.
把你J榈乃有C交oCO
The financial district's under their jurisdiction.
金融部分是他裁Q的
Don't you get it? This case is talking to us!
你不明白? @案子是我管的
I'm a peacock, Captain! You gotta let me fly on this one!
我是只孔雀 L官 你@次得我w一下吧
You know what, Terry? Let's just settle this. Peacocks don't fly.
你知道 特Y? 我e了 孔雀不w
They fly, they fly a little bit.        Yeah, about as much as a penguin.
他就w那N一c      是 像企Z那
One more thing, do me a favor, don't go chasing waterfalls.
有事 臀忙 e逞能
Was that accidental, or were you trying to quote TLC on purpose?
是意外 是你只有意引述TLC的歌?
I don't even understand the reference.
我都不知道你在f什N
You don't understand what you said?        I don't know what that is.
你不知道你f了什N?      我不知道那是什N
Get out.        Go.
出去      好吧
How did they get that story?
他怎N知道@事的?
I'm tired of being treated like a jerk for trying to do the right thing.
我真是┩噶吮划做弄巧成拙的笨蛋了
Hey, guys.
嘿 夥
There's a proxy vote for a big reinvestment of the pension coming up,
有一退休金的大型再投Y目的代理投票
so if you just wanna come by the old...        Damn it, Bob!
如果你想^老...      去你的 U勃
Let me ask you something.
我你件事
What do you even do around here besides interrupt people?
除了打e人 你贮ce的事?
Well, I serve as treasurer to the union.
好吧 我是工的罩鞴
I make a wicked pot of decaf.
我煮了一o咖啡因咖啡
Exactly! You're a worthless piece of shit!
正是 你一o是
Probably right, Terry. That's why I feel so sad all the time.
也S]e 特Y @就是樯段铱是很y^的原因
I'm gonna go for a walk.
我出去走走
Bob!        Say something.
U勃      fc什N
Come on! Bob!
回 U勃
I didn't mean it, all right? I'm upset.
我不是那意思 好? 我很生
Actually, we don't do that here. This is an installation art piece.
其 我不放在@ @是一安b的g品
This coffee table?        Yes. We don't put drinks on it.
@咖啡桌?      是的 我不在@上面放料
Five hundred thousand?        He can read! Congratulations.
50f?      他看得懂 恭喜
What?        I'm sorry, are you in the right place?
什N?      抱歉 你Φ胤搅?
Or not? I'm...
是走e了? 我...
Terry.        Does he... Okay.
特Y      他...好吧
Well...        Sorry. Terry! What are you doing here?
好吧      Σ黄 特Y 你磉@?
I want to be with you.        No, Terry, that's not gonna happen.
我想和你在一起      不 特Y @不可能
You know where you belong. On top of me in the Poconos.
你知道你凫赌难Y 波克山 躺我的身上
Instead, you're here selling dirty coffee tables?
而F在 你s在@u@v不拉\的咖啡桌?
I mean, look at this. This is nonsense!
我是f 看看 @|西不知所^
Terry, this is an original Haverfield-Jameson.
特Y @Y哈弗菲德-詹姆森的原作
The chaos of the coffee table? It represents our fractured egos.
混y的咖啡桌? 表示我破碎的自尊
You think I don't know about this artsy-fartsy crap?
你J槲也徽JR@假bg家的拉圾?
This coffee table isn't the ego.
@咖啡桌不是什N谑沧拥淖宰
It represents our shattered sense of community
它表示在Y本主x主У呐c世隔^的面前
in the face of capitalist-driven isolation.
我大y七八糟的品味
Looks like the work of Cindy Sherman
看起硐袷切恋稀ぶx曼
or Frank Stella.
或是弗m克・斯特拉的作品
How did you know that, Terry?
你怎N知道@ 特Y?
I took some classes at RISD
我在_德uOW院上了滋谜n
so I could make fun of these lame artsy douches in my neighborhood.
@游铱梢匀⌒ξ亦居那些差诺募偎g家
Terry, lower your voice!        I don't have to lower my voice.
特Y 音小c      我嵋f小c
Is this man bothering you?
@男人在}_你?
Are you actually having sex with this creep?
你和@鬼上床了
Terry, he's gay. Okay?
特Y 他是同志 好不?
He's even wearing a T-shirt that says, "I'm gay"!
他甚至穿了件 "我是同志"的T恤
All right? And also, he is my boss.
好? 有 他是我老
Happy for you, man. Good.
槟愀吲d 小子 好吧
Can you get out of here now? I'm talking to my lady.
你F在可以走_? 我在和我的女人f
Mr. Reger, everything is fine. Terry is actually leaving now.
瑞格先生 ]事的 特Y正要走了
Nice toot, sailor.        Jesus.
嘟嘟得不e 水手      老天
Terry, what are you doing?
特Y 你在?
Look, I waited three years for you to be more than a cop, okay?
著 榱俗你事I有所l展 我等了你三年
Just give me one more year.
再多o我一年
Terry, you don't get another year. I'm done.
特Y ]有再一年了 我完了
Fine.
好吧
Terry, don't touch that! Terry!        Oh, my God!
特Y e碰那 特Y      哦 我的天啦
I don't need this shit. I don't need you!
我不需要@破玩意 我不需要你
And when you call me, I'm not coming back!
有你再打o我 我也不回
Oh, boy! Over the top!        How outr?
哦 小子 好正的1哦      好男人
I'll burn this bitch down to the ground!
我要把@破玩意成粉碎
Fresh! Energetic!        I love his rawness!
有生 有活力      我喜g他的直接
Stop critiquing me, okay? I'm a human being! I'm not a piece of art!
eur我了 好? 我是人 我不是件g品
Yes, you are.        Bravo!
是的 你是的      好哇
I'm a peacock flying into a rainbow!
我是w越彩虹的孔雀
Yes! Yes!
是的 是的
These braised short ribs taste like a dog's asshole.
@跖Ｐ∨L起硐窆菲ü
Sweetie.        You know what, I'm sitting here thinking,
你知道 我坐在@Y想
"Who in the world would slow roast a dog's asshole
@世界有l慢慢豕菲ü
"and serve it to their husband?"
o他的老公吃?
You would.        You are being awful. What's wrong?
你的      你太可怕了 怎N了?
Captain took us off the case.        I'm sorry.
L官不我查那案子      我很z憾
I told Terry about my dark days in college,
我告V特Y我在大W的黑暗日子
and it brought up some feelings.
我感|良多
Well, honeydick, that was a long time ago.
好吧 H鄣 那是很久以前了
You're not that same person you were.
你已不是之前那你了
No, you don't get it. There is a darkness inside of me.
不 你不明白 我刃挠耗
It wants to get out. It wants to walk around.
它想出 出碜咦
It wants some walking around money, and it wants to buy some shoes.
它想四[弄cX 想I些鞋子
And it wants to walk up with the people and say,
它想要和人走f
"Hey, Gator don't play no shit. "
"嘿 w特不是f著玩的"
You feel me?        Yeah.
你明白?      是的
Gator never been about that, never been about playing no shit.
w特牟@ 牟f著玩的
Sweetie, I'm sorry.        It's okay.
Σ黄      ]事
I just...        Remember that night we met?
我只是...      得我相遇的那晚上?
The attending physician told me,
主治t生告V我
"We got a drugged-out pimp in the back. "
"後院有嗑的皮l客"
And I went back there, and I pulled open that curtain,
我去到後院 打_窗
You were weak, scared,
你脆弱 害怕
ass up, inflamed, crying.
糟透了 l炎 心地哭著
At that moment, I knew.
那r候 我知道
"Hey, he's no pimp. Pimps don't cry. "
"嘿 他不是皮l客 皮l客才不哭呢"
Pimps don't cry
皮l客不哭
No they do not
不 他不
They don't shed a tear
他不流I
Pimps don't cry
皮l客才不哭
Come lay with me.
我去床上躺躺
Be safe, and let's make love. Come on.
你有安全感 我碜 戆
Every time you say, "Be safe," it tears me apart.
每次你f安全感 都我心欲^
You gotta let me be who I'm gonna be.
你得我成槲乙成榈娜
Allen, I'm pregnant.
艾 我言辛
Whose baby is that?
是l的孩子?
Who's the man who did that to you?
是哪男人把你肚子搞大的?
Gator's bitches better be using jimmies!
w特的女人都用套子
I'm sorry. See, that's what I'm talking about.
Σ黄 看我都f的什N啊
Oh, my God.
哦 老天
You need to leave.
你走吧
Get out! Get out, Allen! Get out!
L L出去 艾 L出去
Hey
嘿
Hey. What are you doing here?
嘿 你在@?
Come here when I have lady troubles,
我有女人的}的r候就磉@
which means I come here about every night.
也就是f我每晚都磉@
What are you doing here?
你在@Y?
Sheila and I got into it tonight.
希拉今晚和我吵了一架
She threw me out.
她把我s出砹
Well, you're not a cop
好吧 直到你老婆把你踢出家
till your wife throws you out of the house, partner.
你都不是警察 老兄
Does it bother you that the Castien robbers
你在意卡斯蒂劫案
only took 74 grand in diamonds?
只ё吡似呷f四的石?
They're junkies. Who cares? I mean...
他是垃圾 l在乎? 我是f
I don't know if a junkie can go down a 20-story zipline, though.
不^ 我不知道一垃圾不降低
How are you going?
你怎N?
We're about to have us a little screw party in this red Prius over here
我湓谀翘t色普J斯Y搞小派
if you wanna join us.
如果你意加入的
You're not going anywhere near that Prius, okay?
e靠近那台普J斯 好?
Here's what we're talking about. We're talking about a bunch of hobos
我的意思是 一群v兮兮的
with fingers in each other's pooper
oI[民
in a stranger's car with talk radio playing really loud.
在陌生人的子Y大放V播
It's gonna be a nice evening.
今晚很不e
Well, we're not participating in that. We have no interest.
好吧 我不⒓ 我]d趣
Let me rephrase it.
我再f一遍
We got a jar of old mustard, and we got a poodle,
我有一罐老芥茉u 一b卷毛狗
and we're just get in there and we're gonna put some D's in some A's.
我^去 然後在上面些"D" "A"什N的
Hey, are you Dirty Mike and the boys?
嘿 你是t⒏绾退的兄弟?
How do you know who we are?        You left a note in that car.
你咋知道我是l?      你在攘袅l
Police, shithead.        He's a copper. We gotta go. Come on!
警察 笨蛋      他是警察 我R上走 快呀
Hey! Goose it, boys! They're cops!
嘿 快c走 小子 他是l子
Rub your dicks on the car as you're running away!
跑的r候 在那上搞c破
You turned my beautiful Prius into a nightmare!
你把我漂亮的普J斯成碾y
We are gonna have sex in your car! It will happen again!
我在你上做 再l生的
I don't know where I'm gonna sleep tonight.
我不知道我今晚要睡哪
Fortunately, I know where you're gonna be drinking.
幸\的是 我知道我要去哪喝酒
Jack of All Trades. Drinks on me. Come on.
f事通 我客 走吧
No, I already have a beer.        No, no, no, no.
不 我已有瓶啤酒了      不 不 不 不
I'm talking about doing some serious drinking.
我f的是真的喝酒
Drinking with Terry Hoitz.
和特Y・霍喝酒
This sucks, man. Work our ass off on this case,
真不爽 兄弟 我查@案子屁L尿流
now we gotta hand over all of our evidence?
F在我要交出所有C?
Yeah, it's not right.
是 是不爽
Oh, my God, I'm hungover.
哦 老天 我宿碎
So, you guys are law enforcement?
所以 你是谭ú块T?
Yeah, we're an independent government agency who,
是 我是立政府部T
along with the FBI and the Federal Reserve,
`凫FBI和美
regulate the stock market and corporate fraud.
管理股票市龊推I欺p
And the Federal Reserve is a prison?
@美κ且凰Oz?
No, basically, it's a held-for-profit bank that sets interest rates
不 它是一家O定利率和J款o其它y行的
and loans money to other banks.
盈利性y行
Is that a wastebasket?        Yeah, right there.
那是垃圾桶?      是的 就在@
Thank you.
xx你
You all right?        Holy hell!
你]事吧?      老天呀
I'm so sorry.
真的很抱歉
I got so drunk last night.
我昨晚喝太醉了
I think I thought a tube of toothpaste was astronaut food.
我想我把一管牙刷成太空人食物
Come on in, fellas.
M戆 兄弟
You gotta be kidding me. You're Ershon's lawyer.
_玩笑吧 你是厄森的律
We're turning over our investigation to you?
我把我的{查Y料o你?
Let me assure you there will be no conflict of interestewx
我向你保C 我和大l・厄森之g
between me and David Ershon.
]有利益n突
And if this were an actual investigation,
如果有|性的{查
I would immediately recuse myself.
我立即避嫌退出
This is all the evidence we have,
@是我所有的C
and I truly hope you take this seriously.
我真心希望你能J真Υ
Yes. Very much so.
是 的
From everything I've heard, I understand
我所知 我t解到
you guys are the best at these types of investigations.
你在此{查上是最棒的
Outside of Enron and AIG
除了安然和美H集F
and Bernie Madoff,
有伯{德・道夫
WorldCom, Bear Stearns, Lehman Brothers.
世界 斯登 雷曼兄弟
Okay. Thank you. Thank you, Detective.
好的 xx你 xx你 探T
Would you like a seat, or you're fine?        No, I'm good.
你要不要坐下 是你站著?      我站著就好
Okay. Let me just assure you fellas,
好吧 我向你保C
David Ershon is an upstanding citizen.
大l・厄森是一正直的公民
I am playing squash with him tonight at the club,
我今晚要和他在俱凡看虮谇
and we're having dinner.
我要吃晚餐呢
You listen to me, you Windsor knot-wearing monkey,
你o我著 你@些税褓F族的猴子
you play squash with Ershon, right?
你和厄森一起打壁球 ?
Your kids go to school with his?
你小孩和他小孩上同一gW校?
How would you know if he's clean or not?
你怎N知道他是不是清白?
I will take a look at your evidence,
我看看你的C
and I will take a second look at the financials.
另外我再查一下r
And when I come back and bust your ass,
我再回碚夷懵┑r候
we're locking David Ershon in the Federal Reserve!
我把大l・厄森PM美
He still doesn't understand the concept.
他是不明白@^念
What are you doing?
你在?
We just handed all of our evidence over
我把我所有的C
to the bad guy's lawyer!
都交o那牡暗穆
Are you a big man, huh?
你是大人 嗯?
I'm talking to you.        What?
我在和你f      什N?
You wake up in the morning, you say,
你清早起 你f
"I'm putting on my big boy pants"?
"我要穿上大男孩的子?(比喻他幼稚)
"Look, I'm wearing a belt!
"看 我M了皮
"I've got big boy pants on!"        No!
"我穿上了我男孩的子"      不是
You borrow a little jacket, you go?
你借一件小A克 你去呀?
You take your lunch 'cause you got big boy pants on?
就因槟愦┝舜竽泻⒌难子 所以你吃午餐?
You got your big boy pants and your snack?
你有了大男孩的子 有你的食物?
I could say big, loud things!
我可以大 狂吼地f
I could be demonstrative!
我可以表_感情
Stop!        We don't, we don't do this!
停下      我不是 我不是@幼龅
You're scaring the shit out of me, man! Stop it!
你奈伊 兄弟 停下
Is this how you conduct yourself? In a democracy?
你就是@N控制自己的? 在民主社?
What the hell are you doing, man?
你到底在 兄弟?
I'm so tired of you getting angry and yelling all the time.
我只是受蛄四憧是生 y吼y叫
It's exhausting.
我]精力了
I feel like I'm partners with the Hulk.
我X得我是G巨人的搭n
You wanna know why I'm so angry all the time?
你想知道我槭颤N是生?
'Cause the more I try and do right, the more I screw things up.
因槲以绞窍胱Φ氖 我越搞砸
We've got a possible jumper at 3 World Financial Center, 23rd floor.
世界金融中心323怯幸伤铺堑娜
All units, fire department, en route.
所有部T 火警部T R上^去
SEC.        Beaman's office.
C券交易      比曼的k公室
We have to go.
我得^去
But the Captain.        We have to go, Allen.
但是L官      我得^去 艾
All units, I need a respondent.
所有部T 我需要回
Possible jumper, 3 World Financial Center.
世界金融中心3 疑似跳钦
Shit. It's Beaman!
靠 是比曼
He's gotta know something.        Wesley!
他一定知道些事情      f斯利
Detective Hoitz and Gamble. We got this.
霍探T和甘博探T 我硖理
I took an online class at University of Phoenix on negotiating.
我在P凰城大W上了堂判的在n程
I'm gonna need a priest and a bullhorn.
我需要一牧和一U音器
I got no bullhorn.        Does anyone have a bullhorn?
我]有U音器      有人有U音器?
Bullhorn, anyone?        Truck.
U音器 有人有?      卡
Police business. I need to use your PA system.
警察理公 我需要使用你的U音C
Okay, let me turn it on.
好的 我把它打_
Mr. Beaman? Mr. Don Beaman?
比曼先生? 唐・比曼先生?
It's Wesley. I know Ershon's Wesley's...
是f斯利 我知道厄森的f斯利...
Look, there's a lot to live for in this life.
著 你的生命中有很多值得活下淼|西
A lot of great things, like soda pop, big fresh can of soda pop.
很多ゴ蟮|西 像是汽水 大支新r的罐b汽水
They do not care!
他不在乎
Give me this. I know how to talk to him.
把@o我 我知道怎N和他f
Listen, we all know you're a scumbag, and nobody cares about you.
著 我知道你是卑鄙的砘 ]人在乎你
Rotten piece of shit.
一坨臭屎
That's worse than what I was saying.
比我f的更差
I'm not gonna lie to you, Don.
我和你f真 唐
People down here are starting to murmur
@下面的人正_始嘀咕
that you don't have the balls to do it.
你]有子跳
I don't care!        Yeah.
我不在乎      是呀
I say you can do it.
我知道你能做到的
I mean, I don't want you to jump.
我是f 我不想要你跳
I'm just saying you have the capability.
我只是f你有@能力
Look, he's flying!
看 他w起砹
Stop that.
e吹了
Half empty bottle of gin. Chair knocked over.
半瓶杜松子酒 椅子碰翻了
Look at this, it's a clear sign of a struggle.
看看@ @是很明@暝的E向
Make sure you get this, all right?
要把@拍下 好?
Detectives, all your work's done here. You can go.
探T @Y]你什N事了 可以走了
What about Ershon targeting the lottery?
如果厄森的目苏是彩票呢?
You know why Ershon was calling down
你知道槭颤N厄森
to the lottery offices all those times?
@子一直打去彩票k公室N?
Because he was hooking up with the Powerball girl,
因樗勾搭上了@力球女孩
the one on TV with all the numbered balls.
上L球的那
Yeah. She filed a restraining order on him last week.
是 她上周申了法院制止令
It was right there in front of you the whole time.
是r候面和你f了
Can't be.        You guys are getting transferred.
不吧      你被{走了
What?        Traffic.
什N?      交警
Yeah, that's right.
是 ]e
You, you're gonna walk a beat downtown.
你 你要在城热粘Ｑ策
You're gonna walk a beat downtown.
你要在城热粘Ｑ策
It's done. No.        Captain, what are you talking about?
f完了 不       L官 你在f什N
No, no. It's done.
不 不 f完了
Save yourselves some gas.        Captain!
o你省c油      L官
Is there an appeal process we can...
我有]有申V程序
Had to do what you had to do, Captain.
你得做你做的 L官
Wow! That hurt.
哇 真K的
Excuse me. Where's my car?        They towed it.
不好意思 我哪去了      他拖走了
Couple of homeless people were messing around in it.
一些o家可w的人在上面vy
That's an official police car.        Could have fooled me.
那是一v正式的警      也就__我
Wow, Mauch was upset, huh?
哇 毛奇很生 嗯?
Really?
是?
The only thing I had to be proud of in my life
我在我老婆面前唯一值得傲的事
was being a detective.
就是我了探T
That was all I had. Now it's gone.
我只有@了 F在@也]了
I know. I know. You still got me.
我知道 我知道 你有我
Don't you get it? I don't want you, Allen, okay? I never did.
你不明白? 我不需要你 我矶疾恍枰你
I told you that scaffolding violation was dogshit.
我告V^你 _手架`的事是狗屎
I can't believe you still doubt me after everything we've seen.
我不敢相信 我至诉@N多事後 你是|疑我
It's a real case, and I'm a real cop.
@是真的案子 我是真警察
We just got the wrong target for Ershon.
我只是查e了方向
You carry a rape whistle.        This is real cop work.
你Я税焉谧      @是真警察的工作
There is nothing about you that makes a man a man, okay?
你就]有做^一件男人做的事情 好?
You got no gun, no car, no wife, and now you got no partner.
你]有 ]有 ]老婆 F在你拍跻]了
Leave me alone.
我为呆
A mutt case.
一蠢案子
Terry, I am a cop, for your information, okay?
特Y 告V你 我是警察 好?
A broken partnership.
散伙的拍n
I'm a cop!
我是警察
And getting busted down to a shitty assignment.
被降到一差诺墓ぷ
Allen and Terry hit the trifecta.
艾和特Y中了"三B彩"了
But sometimes when you get your ass kicked,
但是有r候 你倒霉的r候
that's when you find out what's real...
@就是你lF真的r候
...and what needs doing.
需要做什N的r候
Whether it's directing traffic...
不管是指]交通
Come on!
走呀
...or cracking a multibillion dollar fraud.
是破了装偃f的p_案
Do you work here?        Yeah, I do.
你在@Y上班?      是 ]e
The wrecking ball that crashed into Castien down there.
那那撞上卡斯蒂的起重球
They also did damage to your office?
也δ愕霓k公室造成p?
Some police officers came by and sealed it off.
一些警察^戆阉封上了
Do you recall what they looked like?
你得他L什N?
One of them had an Australian accent.
其中一有澳洲口音
You don't happen to do any business for the state lottery, do you?
你不是在州彩票工作吧?
No. Our main client is Lendl Global.
不是 我的主要客羰翘m道公司
Can I ask what this is about?
可以下是怎N回事?
TRAFFIC ENFORCER OF THE MONTH
本月交警之星
Terry Hoitz
特Y・霍
Gator needs his gat, you punkass bitch!
w特需要他的 你o能的v人
'Cause that's what a real cop is.
因檎婢察就是@N回事
No, I didn't say "Lock her up. " I never said, "Lock her up. "
不 我]f把她P起 我^]f^"把她P起"
A guy who does what needs to be done.
一男人做了他做的事情
A guy who knows how to use his dark side for good.
一男人知道怎N善用他的黑暗面
And then you move to Florida.
然後搬去佛_里_
One, two, three, attack!
一 二 三 M攻
Terry, it's me.
特Y 是我
Tap out. Tap out.        It's me, Allen.
放_我 放_我      是我 艾
Are you tapping out, or are you hitting me in the face?
你放不放_ 是你要打我的?
I'm tapping out!
我放_了
You crazy? What are you doing, man?
你了? 你在@ 兄弟?
They might be watching us.        Could've killed you.
他可能在O我      我可能⒘四
Turn out the lights.        What?
P      什N?
They could be watching us.        Who?
他可能在O      l?
I found some big information, okay?
我lF一些重要的消息 好?
About what?        Some scary shit, Terry. This is big.
P於什N?      重要信息 特Y @天大秘密
How'd you get in here? This place is foolproof.
你怎NM淼? @地方有安全自ib置的
We can't be too careful.        What are you talking about?
我得更小心      你在f什N?
This place might be bugged.        There's no bugs in here.
@地方可能被`      @Y]有`器
First off, I missed you.
首先 我想你
What's going on?        Did you hear what I said?
l生什N事了?      你到我f什N了?
Fine, I kind of missed you, too.        Thank you.
好吧 我也有c想你      xx
Okay. I found out whose losses Ershon has to cover.
好吧 我知道厄森在掩wl的p失
It's Lendl Global.        What?
是m道公司      什N?
Lendl staged the Castien robbery as a distraction
m道用卡斯蒂劫案分散注意
so they could break into their own accounting firm next door.
所以他可以JM他隔壁自己的事账
They then altered all the records to cover the losses
然後他{Q了硌谏w
that Ershon had cost them through all of his bad investments.
厄森投Y失〉p失
You're not supposed to be doing this.
你不做@事的
You're supposed to be walking the beat.
你巡街的
I know. Pretty tricky, though, huh?
我知道 不^很C智吧 嗯?
This is bad, Allen. This is bad.
@不好 艾 @不好
No wonder the captain wanted us to stay out of this.
y怪L官想我不要管@
Yeah, I bet Beaman started asking questions.
是的 我想比曼_始|疑了
That's why they killed him.        Man.
@就是他⑺的原因      老天
Here's the other thing.
有件事
Tomorrow, there's a massive business deal going down.
明天 有一未笊意
Ershon's leading it.
厄森主
I still can't figure out
我是不知道
who the poor sucker is they're making the deal with,
他在和哪可z的砘镒錾意
but we gotta stop it.
但是我得阻止@紊意
It's time to let the peacock fly.
是r候孔雀w起砹
I'm not going, Allen. I like what I do.
我不去 艾 我喜g我F在做的
So do I. We're cops.
我也是 我是警察
No. I like what I do now. I like working traffic. It's a great gig.
不 我喜g我F在做的 我喜g做交警 很不e
What?
什N?
I like working traffic. I'm not going with you.
我喜g指]交通 我不和你去
What is this traffic bullshit?
指]屁交通?
What are you talking about?        I'm talking about my life.
你在f什N?      我在f我的人生
The corner I run on 54th and 3rd Avenue? It hums.
我管的54街和第3大道的路口 很忙的
It's Terry's intersection. And the traffic guys? They're good guys.
@是特Y的十字路口 其交警呢? 他是好人
There's this one guy, Phillip? He can pee in the urinal from 20 feet.
有一砘 菲利浦? 他可以x便池20英尺尿尿
You've gotta see it, Allen. You've got to.
你得看看 艾 你得看看
What happened to you? What happened to this being our time?
你怎N回事? 我的r光怎N了?
No way, Allen. I'm out. I'm done.
不行 艾 我退出 我不至
Get in the car.        Come on, Allen. We both know it's wooden.
上      拜 艾 我都知道@是木
Apartment pop. Now get in the car.        You're not gonna shoot me.
x_@ F在上      你不_打我的
Okay, I'll be honest. This is only the second time I've ever fired this.
好吧 我老f @是我第二次_
So stop pointing it at me.
那e指著我了
Look, tomorrow morning, all I know is I'm going to Mauch, all right?
著 明天早上 我只知道我要去找毛奇 好?
For what? He doesn't care.
榱耸颤N? 他不在乎
He's been dodging this case for too long and I want answers.
他避@案子很久了 我需要答案
I want him to look me in the eye and tell me why.
我要他看著我的眼睛 告V我槭颤N
Turn on the news, man. Nobody cares.
看看新 兄弟 ]人在乎
I hope I'm not alone.
我希望我不是一人
Hope you bring it.
希望你能上子
We got a big day out there. Big one.
今天是重大的日子 大日子
We got a full moon. People are gonna be amped, all right?
是M月 人很有物j的 好?
Let's see what we got on hot tips, all right?
我砜纯从惺颤N衢T的提示 好?
The new bathmats are in.
新的浴室防滑|M砹
One more thing. We got a serial rapist in Crown Heights.
有件事 我在皇家高地有一BhΨ
Jeez, I'm sorry. That's from my other job. Ignore that. Forget that.
老天 Σ黄 @是我另外的工作 e管它 e管
Well, don't ignore it.
好吧 也不要不管
If you live in Crown Heights, you know, walk in pairs.
如果你住在皇家高地的 你知道 Y伴同行
Gene Mauch to kitchen accessories.
吉恩・毛奇去N房配件^
I gotta go. Go get 'em. Let's be careful out there.
我得走了 加油 在外面小心c
The oak.
橡漕
I like to keep the oak together and the maple separately, okay?
我想要把橡漕的放一起 和漕分_ 好?
And these chopping boards?
有@些切菜板?
Hey, Captain.
嘿 L官
Hey, Allen. Hey, how you doing?
嘿 艾 怎N?
What are you doing here? Are you here for the bathmats?
你? 碣I新的浴室防滑|?
I need you to be straight with me.        Straight with us.
我需要你坦白告V我      我之g坦白
Hey, Terry. Look at this.
嘿 特Y 看看你z
I thought you were working traffic today.        Let them block the box.
我以槟阋指]交通      他堵著吧
Besides, partners' code, right?        Thanks.
另外 搭n章程 Π?      xx
Hey, why have you worked your ass off trying to kill this case?
嘿 槭颤N你非要⑦@案子K止?
All right, fine. I'm gonna tell you guys something.
好吧 好吧 我砀嬖V你些事情
You really went into deep water on this one. You really went in deep.
你真的查得很深 查得很深
Ershon's connected to all the higher ups,
厄森和上佣加新j
and I gotta save what little ass I have left, okay?
我得樽约毫l後路 好?
You keep hiding from shit in the world,
m然你F在一直ν饨珉[m@些av的事情
and eventually the world comes to your front door.
但最K事情是被揭l的
Nice.        That's very nice.
很好      f得真好
I heard it in an episode of Touched By An Angel.
@是我哪臣《天使在人g》YW淼奶ㄔ~
You keep this thing real quiet,
如果你能悄悄地{查@事
and you make sure you have real evidence,
K找到_的C
and maybe I'll see what I can do.
那或S我可以看看有什N能偷蒙厦Φ
But if you make a lot of noise
但如果你大旗鼓
and you attract the media attention, and you bring the DA in on this,
引砻襟w的注意 把地方z察官也砍哆M
I am out, okay?
那就不用碚椅兔α 明白了?
Yeah, we'll go in there like church mice.
行 我安o得像教堂Y的老鼠一
But there's one case, one case in a career
但I生涯中有那N一案子
where you go all in. This is it.
是他AM全力去{查的 F在就是@
All right. Then you do us proud.
很好 那就做o我看吧
'Cause I don't want no scrubs.
因槲也恍枰"二流警探"
Really?        No.
真的?      是的
You're not aware that's a TLC song?
你]lF@是首TLC逢的歌?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我不知道你在f什N
Second time.        You said chasing waterfalls,
第二次了      你f不要逞能
now you're saying you don't want no scrubs.
F在你又f你不需要二流警探
I don't even understand the reference.        It's like a tic.
我都不知道那是什N淼      @是口^U
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我不知道你在f什N
Remember, this thing gets messy, we never talked.
住 如果@事捅渥恿 就我奈凑^@事
You can trust us.        Real quiet.
你可以相信我      必暗地Y行事
You gotta creep. Creep.
小心慎 悄o息知道
Come on.
又砹
You don't say "Creep-creep"
除非你是在引用TLC的歌~
unless you're quoting TLC.
不然你不f"悄o生息"
Hey, guys.
嘿 夥
You know Danson and Highsmith were not good cops, right?
你知道丹森和海史密斯不是好警察吧?
Yeah, I guess we kind of knew that, but it's a drag.
是的 我知道 但也是]k法的
I mean, at a certain point, who's left to be a hero?
我是f 剩下的人Y有l能做英雄呢
Not to be corny, maybe it's you guys.
m然我不想f 但有可能是你z
You ready?
你浜昧
Yeah.        Let's go.
好了      我走
No, but the highlights are great.        Thank you.
不 挑染的部分很好看      xx
Sexy but serious.        Thank you.
性感但又很f重      xx
Excuse me.
打_一下
Who the hell are all these people? I was only expecting one man.
@他都是些什N人? 我只想一人而已
You know, they're just some people I owe money to who wanted to be here.
呃 就是一些人我欠了他X 他自己要淼
Who are they?
他是l?
Well, they are some Chechen patriots, entrepreneurs.
呃 臣的一些者 有一些企I家
And the black chaps are some businessmen from Nigeria.
然後那些黑人小伙子是哪崛绽淼
You owe money to the Nigerians and Chechens?
你欠尼日利人跟臣人的X?
Yes. Yes, I do.
呃 是的 我欠他X
You're a piece of work.        Thank you.
你有上伦勇      xx
Probably best to get started.
我最好是_始吧
This is good, baby. We're in the game, we know the score.
@硬诲e 夥 我已入局了 而且知道比分
The only thing that bugs me is
唯一我不爽的是
we still don't know who Ershon's targeting.
我是不知道厄森的目耸鞘颤N
Is it the lotto? Who is it?
是彩票? 幕後又是l?
Who cares? Some rich prick.
l在乎? 肯定是某有X的蠢蛋
I have to tell you, I am tremendously excited by this deal.
我必告V你 我於@交易很d^
And I can assure you that every dime of your money
我可以跟你保C你投入的每一分X
will be invested with the utmost diligence.
都⒈蛔畲笙薅鹊睦用
Your rates of return are really exciting.
你o出的回舐蚀_很人d^
We think our members are gonna be just thrilled.
我的成T一定眼前一亮
Yeah. I mean, we've averaged, like, 18% over the last 10 years.
是的 ^去十年的平均回舐  差不多有18%
All right. Quiet as a church mouse, in and out.
我F在要像教堂的老鼠 安o得M去再出
I can feel that tingling in my balls you were talking about.
我F在可以感受到你f的那N蛋疼的性^
Beautiful.
很好
All right, listen up.
好了 你著
I am Detective Gamble. This is Detective Hoitz.
我是甘博探T @位是霍探T
We need your cooperation.
我需要你的配合
David Ershon.
大l・厄森
You're under arrest for fraud, embezzlement,
你因p_和污
and in connection to the murder of Don Beaman.
以及涉嫌唐・比曼被⒁话副徊读
This is a bad idea.
@不是好主意
Hey, guys.
嘿 夥
Bob? What are you doing here?
U勃? 你在@质颤N?
I'm investing.
我在投Y啊
Do you remember we talked about that proxy vote a while back?
你得我之前到的代理人投票那事?
This is what it was for.        Holy shit.
f的就是@事      鬼
It's a more aggressive investment strategy for the pension.
@只是一更冒U的嵝艚鹜顿Y
Allen! We're the suckers. They're targeting the police pension fund.
艾! 我太蠢了 他的目耸蔷察的嵝艚
Gentlemen, you're here illegally and without a warrant.
先生 你o磉@ 而且也]有授嗔
We are within our rights to take action.
我有袢⌒
So much for quiet as church mice!
不能再像教堂Y的老鼠了!
Go!
跑!
Who the hell are those guys?
那些人他的到底是l?
Gentlemen,
先生
I can get you obstructed view tickets for Rock of Ages.
我可以搞到uL年代的票 不^野不太好
Even I admit that's not very tempting,
m然我也承J那]吸引力
but I'm not made of tickets, God damn it!
但我也不是什N票都能弄到的 死的!
Get in the front!        How do you start this freaking thing?
到前座去      你是怎N想到的?
Go on! Go!
快c!快!
Shit!        Go!
的!      快_!
Oh, my...
哦 天...
Jeanie! Get over here! You, go get the bloody car!
吉妮! ^! 你 去把_!
Hold the wheel!
抓住方向P!
Open the back!        I got it. I got it!
打_後湎!      知道了 我知道了!
They're gonna kill me. And then they will kill you.
他⒘宋 然後再⒛
Well, I'm gonna kill you first!        And then they will kill me.
我先⒘四愕!      然後他再⑽乙淮
We have two rogue police officers. They are armed and dangerous,
F有擅游手好f的警察 他佩有支很危U
and holding David Ershon hostage.        Stupid pricks!
K且冻至舜笮l・厄森      愚蠢的有X人!
It's us, we're good guys!        Exactly. They're the good guys.
是我 我是好警察      ]e 他是好警察
Where do we go? Where do we go?
我去哪? 我去哪?
I have a small apartment. No one knows about it.
我有一小公寓 ]人知道那
I use it mainly for my parents and prostitutes.
只有我父母跟妓女住^
Not at the same time. That would be wrong.
不是同r 那泳吐┝
Let's hear it from the top, every detail.
你就念^f起吧
I think the best way to tell the story is
我X得v故事的最好方法就是
by starting at the end, briefly,
慕Y尾_始⑹
then going back to the beginning,
然後回到_^
and then periodically returning to the end,
再A段性地Y跟Y尾的PS
maybe giving different characters' perspectives throughout.
或S在^程中o出不同角色的一些^c
Just to give it a bit of dynamism,
@硬疟容^生
otherwise, it's just sort of a linear story.
否t 那就是一握{的故事
Just tell us what happened.
快告V我到底l生了什N事
I lost a bunch of money from some people
我p失掉了某些人的一大PX
and now they want it back.
F在他想要拿回那PX
What about Don Beaman?
那唐・比曼是怎N回事?
Beaman knew that I had falsified my financials,
比曼知道我篡改了一些我的蟊
so they sent down Wesley to try and keep him quiet.
所以他派了f斯利矸馑的口
He forced him at gunpoint to drink a bunch of gin
f斯利用χ他逼他喝了好多杜松子酒
and then forced him onto the ledge.
再把他逼上了窗台
It was only a matter of time before he fell.
他什Nr候掉下去只是rg的}
At least we stopped you from getting the pension fund.
至少我阻止了你得到那P嵝艚
Well, but, yeah, but you didn't. It's already in my account.
嗯 不 你]能阻止 那PX已在我~粞Y了
By 9:00 in the morning, it goes into the Lendl equity fund
到早上9c 那PXR入了m道自有基金
and from there it's transferred to a dozen offshore accounts.
然後哪基金Ro好海外~
By 9:01, it's gone.
9c01分之前 @些X就都被D走
Well, what if we stop the transfer?        But you can't.
那如果我阻止D~呢?      但你不能阻止
What if we stop the transfer?
那如果我阻止D~呢?
You'd have to be at Endemic Bank for 9:00 exactly,
你必在9c整r出F在地方y行
find the clerk, get the routing number.
找到那k事T 拿到分行代
We gotta stop it.
我必阻止@件事
There's no way.
但那不可能
Every cop, the crazy Australian and his crew,
每一警察 有那澳大利子和他的手下
they'll all be after us.
都碜凡段
You could let me go, and I'll give you $10 million each.
你可以放我走 我o你每人一百f
It's not a bribe.        Of course it's a bribe.
@不是VT      @就是VT
You're offering to pay us money to not do our job.
你Do我X我不要完成我的工作
It's not a bribe.
@不是VT
We hang low here tonight. Nobody knows about this place.
我今晚低{行事 ]人知道@地方
We'll be safe. And tomorrow, we hit it.
我很安全 然後明天我就去y行
First things first, I gotta go see Sheila.
但首先 我要去希拉
No way, it's too dangerous.
不行 那很危U
Look, Terry, we don't know what's gonna happen to us tomorrow,
著 特Y 我都不知道明天l生什N
but tonight, I need to make things right with Sheila.
但今晚 我必去希拉λ有交代
All right, go. Go. Be careful.
好吧 去吧 去吧 小心c
Thanks, I will.
xx 我的
Will you say hi to Sheila for me?
你臀腋希拉好?
Okay.        Okay.
好的      很好
Tell her. Say Terry was asking about you.
告V她f 特Y有起^她
He wants to make sure you know
他希望你知道
that he'll be there for you if anything happens.
不管l生什N事他都在你需要r出F的
Yeah.        Drop of a hat, I'm there.
好      危急P^我立R出F
Look, it's starting to get a little weird, man.
著 夥 再往下f就有些奇怪了
If something happens to you, I need to be there to take care of her.
如果你l生了什N事 我必照她
All of her wants, her needs, and desires are now my responsibility.
她所有想要的|西 需求 渴望我都M足她
Why do you say it like it's a predetermined thing?
你致镎f得好像是事先就Q定好的事情?
Just go, man.
去吧 夥
Okay. Thanks.
好的 xx
Go.
去吧
Janeco Gallery.
雅瓤擅佬g^
Francine, it's Terry. Please don't hang up.
弗朗辛 我是特Y e祀
Please pick up.
接吧
Hello.
喂
Hey, sweetie. I was praying you'd be at your mom's house.
嘿 H鄣 我猜你在你家Y
You know what, I can't talk anymore. I think the phone's being tapped.
你知道 我不能f太多 我猜@被`了
Baby, where are you? I wanna see you.
你在哪Y? 我想你
I'm near the place where we did it three Halloweens ago.
我在我上次f}做了三次的那地方
Do you remember?
得?
Okay, yeah, I got it.
哦 得
I'm just warning you, though.
我是砀嬲]你
Watch out. I think they're watching the house.
要小心 我X得他在O你
Don't worry, sweetie. I think I have a way of talking to you.
e心 H鄣 我想我有k法跟你f
I have to admit, I wasn't gonna come. I mean...
我得f 我不想淼 我是f...
After all those years, after the restraining order.
@N多年淼南拗屏钍颤N的
I was worried I might not see you again.
我心我可能再也不到你了
There's some very dangerous people after him,
一些很危U的人在找他
and now they're after us.
F在他在找我
It's just the old lady.
只是老女人
Hello, Allen.
你好 艾
Hello, Mama Ramos. What are you doing out here?
你好 _R斯 你硗饷孀鍪颤N呢?
Sheila said she doesn't know what happened and she wants you back.
希拉f她不明白l生了什N事 她想要你回去
She also says...        Yes.
她f...      嗯
...she wants you on top of her, holding her hair,
...她想你在她的上面 捧著她的^
and riding her like a bucking bronco
像T一匹yZ的R那域T著她
while she sucks your thumb and says, "Mommy likey. "
她吮吸你的大拇指f著"喜g"
You, you tell your daughter...
你告V你的女...
He said he'll always love you.
他f他一直勰
And he's so happy that you're having his child.
他很高d你有了他的孩子
Allen.
艾
He also says that
他f
he wants you to stare into each other's eyes
他要你做那事的r候
without blinking while you do it.
相互看著Ψ降难劬Σ灰眨眼
I love when we do that, Mom.        And then afterward,
我O了我做鄣哪且豢       @之後
lick the sex off each other.
他f要互相口交
I don't wanna do this.
我不想至
You say things that are too personal.
你v太肉麻了
Okay, but just one more thing.
但@是最後一次
She said she loves you,
她f她勰
and wants to hold your hand and have iced tea with you.
想要和你恐手一起喝冰茶
Come on. That's not all she said.
拜 那不是她f的吧
No.
不是
She says other things, but I don't want...        Please, please, please.
她f了e的 但是我不想...      求求你f吧
You don't realize, I may be killed tomorrow.
你不知道 明天我可能就被⒘
Okay.
好吧
She says she wants to unplug all the clocks and the phones
她f她想P掉所有的R和
and have a three-day F marathon.        That's more like it. Yeah.
硪淮稳天的做垴R拉松      @才像她f的
She wants to walk wrong for a week because you guys F'd so hard.
她想一周都下不了床 因槟做得太激烈了
That's just lovely.
太美好了
No more! He says things I can't say.
蛄! 他f的我]法f
It involves a mannequin hand
又是仿真手
and an electric shaver taped to a golf club.
又是高夫球棒 著什N犹牯P刀
Now what'd she say?
她又f了什N?
She says she loves you.
她f她勰
I'm so sorry about everything.
@一切我深感抱歉
And I just had to come here tonight to tell you that I love you.
我今晚只是磉@焊嬖V你 我勰
And the reason why I act like you're a plain wife is that
我把你做一平凡的妻子是因
I'm afraid that if I admit to how stunning
我怕如果我承J你是多N的漂亮
and intelligent and wonderful you are,
多N的明 多N的美妙
I'd just lose you.        Shut up, Allen. I love you.
我就失去你      ef了 艾 我勰
We have a place that's safe. All right.
有很安全的地方
I'm gonna break your hip.
我要操t你的小屁屁
I'm about to do you grandpa-style.
到上啦
I brought some music.
我Я它c阂
Not what I would've chosen, but screw it.
不是我原本想要的 不^就@影
All right. Let's go, Monday morning, time to go to work.
好吧 出l吧 "L一早晨" 工作了
Let's do it.
出l吧
You want my gate code?        Shut up, man!
你要我大T密a?      ]嘴!
That's Wesley!
那是f斯利!
Yes!
成功穿越!
Where'd you learn to drive like that?        Grand Theft Auto!
你哪W磉@娱_的?      《bI手》
Shit, Allen, they're coming.
靠 艾 他砹
Oh, my God!        Shit.
哦 天哪!      靠
Do something, Allen!        Hold on, hold on.
做c什N吧 艾!      住 住
Someone's been playing Grand Theft Auto.
他玩了《bI手》那招啊
I did that!
我成功了!
I did that!        Oh, my God!
我成功了!      哦 天哪!
That's what I'm talking about!        We jackknifed them!
我就f嘛!      他翻D!
Did you see that? It went backwards and then turned upside-down.
看到了? 它向後退然後就翻了
Gator turns vans upside-down
w特把翻了^
like they're in a crazy washing machine!
就好像M了超o诚匆C
Why are you calling yourself Gator?
槭颤N你要叫自己w特?
It's a nickname I had in college. I used to run a dating service.
那是我在大Wr的昵Q 用於一些s服
He was a pimp.        Yeah, I was. I was a pimp.
他是皮l客      是的 我以前是皮l客
Is it me or does it smell like deer vagina in here?
是我身上有味道是本身就一股鹿的道味?
My poor car.
我可z的啊
Right now the streets are a bloodbath.
F在整街^面R一鐾
And, statistically speaking, there's about 30 kids in here,
y了一下 @河写蠹s30名和
10 of you are gonna be dead before your next birthday.
你中的10⒃谀下生日前死去
Got a couple of tips, help you guys stay out of jail.
住c 能你hxOz
One, try your hardest to not be black or Hispanic.
第一 千f不要做黑人或是西班牙人
It's a good tip.        Yeah. Two...
@c不e      嗯 第二...
Gentlemen, we got a hot one.
先生 有情r
Hoitz and Gamble have Ershon hostage, high-speed car chase in progress.
霍和甘博冻至硕蛏 _高速wY在路上
Yes! Gun, gun!
好的!  !
Pass up the guns. Pass them up. Let's go, people.
把鬟^ 鬟^ 出l吧 夥
There we go. Anything, any Tasers? No?
我要走了 l有 ]有
Good. Who wants to go on a ride-along?
很好 l想要一起去?
I do!
我!
All right, you, sweetie. Come on, let's go. Move.
好吧 就你了 甜心 戆 我出l 快
Move! Let's go.        Come on!
快! 出l      快跑!
Cool, a helicopter! Must be covering the high-speed chase.
呆了 有架直升C! 肯定是用砀咚僮粉的
Jesus!
天哪!
Who are those guys?        They're Chechen investors.
那些砘锸钦l?      他是臣投Y商
We were gonna do a Chechen version of Dora the Explorer.
我打算做一《探U家朵拉》的臣版本
Anyway, it went terribly wrong.
不管怎 F在已一F糟了
I feel like it's not fair that they have a helicopter!
他有架直升C @事我X得很不公平!
Oh, no.
哦 不
Damn it.
死的
Watch your head. God, your hair is soft.
注意你的X袋 天哪 你的^好
VO5 Hot Oil.
我用的VO5o素
You're gonna wreck! There's cars coming from both directions!
你@实猛甑! 蛇都有碥
I'm not gonna wreck!
我才不要完蛋呢!
I'm gonna wreck! You're right!        You want me to drive?
我要完蛋了! 被你f中了!      要我黹_N?
This was a very clever idea.        Yeah.
@倒是好主意      是啊
They're gone.
他走了
Let's go.
走吧
They are Nigerians. Yeah, I'd forgotten about them.
他是尼日利人 是啊 我都忘了他了
This is a shortcut.        Are you kidding me?
@是l捷      你在_玩笑吧?
You cannot go down there.
你^不去的
What are you doing?
你在质颤N?
Hit him!
撞他!
Where are we?        Chelsea Pier.
我在哪耗?      切西a^
What the hell?
不是吧?
Jesus!
天啊!
Them having a helicopter is definitely cheating.
他那架直升wC^κ亲鞅
Go!
快走!
Come on!
快跑!
We're cops! Hit the chopper!
我是警察! 打那架直升wC!
This is Martin and Fosse, en route.
我是R丁和佛西 已在路上
Back off! This is our collar!
都退後! @是我的逮捕行!
Set up a perimeter. No arrests until we get there!
拉起防 在我s到前不准袢〈捕行!
Take the light!
把警舸蜷_!
Do not authorize that transfer.
不要批准那D~
This is David Ershon. The transfer is for him.
@是大l・厄森 @な樗D的
He will tell you not to authorize it, okay? Tell him.
他你不要授嗟 快f
Tell him!        Yeah, do as they say. Stop the transfer.
快f!       照他f的做 停止D~
Approve it.
不要停
Now.
就F在
Do not touch anything!
什N都不要!
I swear to God I'll blow your head all over this desk.
我μ彀l誓 我打得你X袋M桌子L
Not a person in this room believes you'll shoot this clerk.
@房gY]人信你_打他
Yeah?
是?
Thank you so much, gentlemen, for the prompt delivery of Mr. Ershon.
非常感x你把厄森先生送^
I have two competing bids from jilted investors.
我有晒P投Y商的r
They're at 30 million, and holding.
它值三千f美金 未到~
Wait! Can't you let me...        Take him away.
等一下! 你就不能我...      把他ё
But computers.
但是算C
What if, one day, they were in charge?
如果有一天它被控制了怎N?
Now if you don't shut up, I will cut your ear off with a butter knife.
如果你F在不]嘴 我用S油刀割掉你的耳朵
That's blunt. Blunt's worse than if it's sharp.
那很g g的比h利的糟糕
Now!
就F在!
You just stood there!
你就站那e!
I didn't know that "now" meant that. How am I supposed to know that?
我不明白"F在"指的是什N 我要怎N知道啊?
I knew what that meant.        Shut up.
我知道是什N意思      ]嘴
You kill us and you kill Ershon. You're out 30 million dollars.
你⒘宋就⒘硕蛏 你就拿不到那三千f了
Who's got the golden goose now, huh?        Yeah.
F在是l咨巷L 啊?      Π
Shit!
鬼!
He's still valuable with a bullet wound, mate.
他就算中了也是有利用r值的
He immediately called your bluff.
他R上就看穿你的把蛄
Get up. And kill the police.
起 ⒘四切┚察
I just wanna make sure I get it right.
我好像搞不清r
Did you want this transfer approved or not approved?
你是要批准D~呢是不批准呢?
You, mate, I'm gonna kill just for fun.
你 夥 我打算⒛憔
Police, don't move! Drop your weapons!
警察 不S! 放下你的武器!
Drop it, or be dropped, homeboy!
要N放下武器 要NM著出去 老弟!
I hope you like the taste of prison food and penis.
我希望Oz的菜和男人能合你胃口
Police! Down on the ground!        Let me see your hands!
警察! 跪地上e!      把手e起!
Hey, hey, you okay?        Hey.
嘿 嘿 你好吧?      嘿
Hey, Gene. Captain. I'm sorry.
嘿 吉恩 L官 很抱歉
I'm sorry.        That's okay. Don't worry about it.
抱歉      ]事 e心
You can call me Gene when we're not in the office.
我不在k公室的r候你可以叫我吉恩
Okay. Thanks for coming by.
好的 xx你能
Attaboy.
好小子
Come on, stay with me. Stay with me.
e@ 我f 我f
We're losing him! We're losing him! He's dying!
他快不行了! 他快不行了! 他快死了!
No. No, no, no, no. I'm just resting.
不不不 我只是在休息
I'm just resting.
我只是在休息
I'm sorry. Did I hurt you?        I'm just resting.
抱歉 我到你了?      我只是在休息
Are you all right?        Just resting.
你好吧?      只是休息一下
Hey, let me tell you something.
嘿 告V你件事
As far as paperwork goes, we'll take care of it.
文案工作我兔ψ龊玫
You know why?        Why?
你知道槭颤N?      槭颤N?
Ain't too proud to beg.
"那是我的s幸"
Come on.
少砹
What?        It's not funny anymore.
怎N了?      不是那N好笑了
I don't know what you're talking about.        TLC references.
不知道你在f什N      TLC的歌名
Still nothing. I swear to you.
啥都不知道 我向你l誓
I'm gonna go over and check on Terry.
我要去那看看特Y
I got a bad knee. Hold on. There you go.
我膝w不太好 住 去啦
It was the king of the mutt cases,
@真是傻瓜案子之最
but Allen and Terry had worked it like stars.
但是艾和特Ys之如
Within 24 hours of learning about Ershon's scheme
24小r都在{查厄森的\
and Lendl's massive losses,
和m道公司的巨大p失
the government issued TARP funds to bail out Lendl.
政府}Ya救助出Y椭m道
Lendl is in everything,
m道涉及各I域
and we're gonna go everywhere...
我aIU展到各地...
They were too big to fail.
出Y巨大不容失
Ershon now resides in Palomino Federal Correctional Facility in Florida.
厄森F在身佛_里_巴洛米Z邦教B所
He still invests. Currency's just different.
他在投Y 只是庞兴不同
Roger Wesley was linked to the Beaman murder
_堋ろf斯利c比曼的\案有P
by security cam footage which Martin and Fosse hadn't checked.
R丁和佛西未z查的O控像
It only showed the back of their heads.
只拍到了他的後X勺
But Allen's Faceback app
但是艾的"人人後X勺"程序
was able to get a match to their faces.
s⑺的正c像ι狭
Terry married Francine.
特Y和弗朗辛Y婚了
He played harp at the reception and it was beautiful.
他在婚Y上奏了Q琴 很美妙
He had learned how to play it in the eighth grade
八年的r候他就W了Q琴奏
to make fun of the fairy that lived up the street.
以嘲笑街的u女
Terry asked Sheila to be his best man, but she declined.
特Y找希拉做他的伴郎 但她拒^了
Let's be honest, we all wanna be superstars and hotshots.
坦白f 我都希望能成榫扌腔蚴桥Ｈ
But guess what?
但知道?
The people that do the real work, the ones that make the difference,
那些在在做事 正改著@世界的人
you don't see them on TV or on the front page.
你不在或是^l上看到他
I'm talking about the day-in, day-outers, the grinders.
我是在f那些日鸵蝗兆鍪碌睦人
Come on, man, you know who I'm talking about: The other guys.
拜 夥 你知道我在fl: 二流人物
See? That's a no-go.        Hey, hey.
看吧? 行不通的      嘿 嘿
You think you broke this Ershon case open?
你以槟破了厄森的案子?
You did nothing.
你什N都]做成
Corporate lobbyists are spending millions
局[f者佑蛋偃f美元
to make sure guys like Ershon keep doing what they do.
以_保像厄森@拥娜丝梢岳^mM行他的勾
Derek Jeter?
德Y克・芴?
Yeah, it's me. You were set up that night you shot me, Terry.
是啊 是我 你_打我那晚被O了 特Y
I told you!        They knew by putting someone like you
我就f嘛!      他知道如果安排一像你@
with a quick trigger finger next to that door
一虞m就_的人
where I do my pre-game walk,
在前通道
it'd end up bad. Bad for both of us.
一定出事 果真我z都倒霉了
Now, I've been doing my own investigation on the banking industry,
F在我在y行I自己做{查
and I was close. I was real close.
很接近了 我就快成功了
So I forgive you, Terry.
所以我原你 特Y
I appreciate that, man. I'm sorry about what happened.
xx 夥 抱歉l生@事
I'm glad you're doing better.
很_心你步入正
The whole damn system is clogged up with dirty money.
整死的系y都被他那些vXo了
And the news doesn't say a word about it. 'Cause who owns them?
新sb字不提 那是因檎l是@幕後主使?
The same corporations that own the government.
和政府幕後相同的人
Courts and the law is all we have left.
法庭和法律是我唯一剩下的途搅
So here's you guys' next case.
所以呢 @是你下一案子
Guy by the name of Carl Bachand, CEO of Killister Bank.
一叫卡・巴尚的人 奇勒斯特y行的CEO
He took three billion in TARP funds.
他挪用了不良Ya救助中的三十|
He's crooked. He's real crooked.
他不是好人 他就是混蛋
Take him down, but be careful. He's got Blackwater mercenaries 24l7.
把他拉下R 但要小心 他有黑水H2417做靠山
Thanks, Derek.
xx 德Y克
Hey, Derek! Wait! What if we need to get in touch with you,
嘿 德Y克! 等等! 如果我想要M你
get some more information or some tickets or something?
要更多消息或是T票什N的怎Nk?
What just happened?
怎N回事啊?
POWEREDY BY 100% VEGETABLE OIL
百分百植物油恿
Goldman Sachs. This case is gonna be nasty.
戈德曼・_克斯 @案子很y搞
Hi. Cute glasses.
嗨 很獾难坨R
What was that?        What?
她f什N?      什N?
What? Dude, what is it with you and hot ladies? What's your secret?
什N? 老兄 你和那辣妹什NPS? 你有秘密?
Honestly, I have no idea what you're talking about.
老f 我不知道你在f什N
Tell me who you lost your virginity to.
告V我你把你的子之身Io了l
She actually became a TV actress. Heather Locklear.
她事上成榱艘幻演T 希瑟・拉克Y
Heather Locklear, what?
希瑟・拉克Y 什N?
You've heard of her?        Come on!
你f^她?      不是吧!
She was much chubbier back then.
她^去要SM
I don't get it. I really, I don't get it.
我想不通 我真是想不通啊
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
破熊字幕M g迎加入
That was you. You don't have a sense of humor.
是你 你]什N幽默感
I do... I have a wonderful sense of humor.
我有... 我不要太有幽默感哦
If you say something funny, I'll laugh.
如果你f些好玩的|西 我笑
All right, I'm gonna tell you a great joke.
好吧 我要o你v很好玩的笑
Please. I love jokes.
戆 我喜g笑
All right. Little boy on his 13th birthday.
好的 有小男孩^13q生日了
It's time to get laid.        Already feels inappropriate.
是r候破了      有c不是r候啊
So he goes to the lady at the whorehouse, he goes, " Miss,
於是他找到妓院Y的小姐 他f"小姐"
"look, I know usually you want money,
"瞧 我知道你通常要收X
"but I don't have any money and it's my birthday.
"但我]X 今天又是我的生日"
"Do you think I could have sex with you for this duck?"
"我能o你@只子然後跟你上床?"
Was he a farmer?        No.
他是r民?      不是
That's probably a Health Code violation,
他可能`反了健康法
bringing a duck into a place of prostitution.
е圾子上妓院
They weren't gonna have sex with the duck!
他不是和那只子上床!
No, I just mean Health Code violation
不 我是fе圾子上那N地方
to have the duck brought into a facility like that.
`抗了健康法
So, anyway, she says, "Yes, I'll do it. "
不管怎 她f"可以"
So he goes in there, gives it to her.
所以他做了 把第一次Io了她
He gives her what?
Io她什N?
The high, hard one! She loves it.
就是又挺又粗的那 她O了
She goes, " You know what?
她接著f "你知道?
"If you do that again, I'll give you your duck back. "
"如果你再做一次 我把你的子o你"
It's like getting laid twice for free.        So... I'm sorry.
所以就是免M上床纱      呃... 抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
The duck is payment for sexual intercourse.        Yes. Yes.
那只子是用砀渡洗驳腻X的      是的是的
Very good.        He used the duck as payment,
很好      他用子付款
and now he's being paid back the duck.
F在他又能把子要回
He goes, " Oh, my God, this is the greatest birthday ever. "
他f"哦 天哪 @是我最棒的生日了"
He does it again.
他又做了一次
Now he's walking home, right? Walking...
然後他走回家了 走走走...
So she was satisfied with duck.
所以她子很M意
With a duck as currency...        Yes.
子做...      是的
...to her. Great. Good.
o她 很棒 很好
So he's walking home,
他走回家去
now he can't wait to get home to tell his father. Right?
F在他迫不及待想要回去告V他爸爸
He's walking down the street with the duck, and all of a sudden, voom,
他和子沿著街道走 突然g Z的一
truck comes by and runs over his duck.
砹溯v 撞倒了他的子
Kills the duck?        Killed the duck.
把子⒘?      ⒘
So the duck is now dead.        The duck is dead.
所以那只子死了      它死了
The kid starts crying, truck driver stops,
那孩子_始哭泣 司C停下了
he's all upset, he didn't mean...        Of course he's crying!
他很┬ 他不是故意的...      他然哭了
He's a 13-year-old boy who's just had sex, twice,
他是13q的孩子 才l生^纱涡越
and he watched his beloved duck die.
他看著自己鄣镍子死掉
Will you shut up and let me tell the story?
你能]嘴我把故事v完?
So far, I don't know how this is ever gonna be funny.
目前橹 我不明白@故事怎N幽默法
The guy feels so bad about killing the duck,
那夥於弄死那只子感到很抱歉
he gives him two dollars.
他o了他KX
And the kid's happy with the two bucks?
那孩子高d了?
He's ecstatic! He got laid twice,
他狂喜不止! 他上床了纱
and now he's got two dollars on top of it.
F在他又得到了KX
Seems like a duck would be worth a lot more than two dollars.
上去一b子h比KX有r值得多
This was a while back. You what I'm...
死了就不值X了
So he goes home, his dad goes, "What happened? What happened?
於是他到了家 他爸爸 "l生什N事了?"
"Tell me! Tell me!"
"告V我! 告V我!"
He goes, "Dad, I got a fuck for the duck,
他f"爸爸 我用子上了床"
"I got a duck for the fuck,
"我又上床拿回了子"
"and I got two bucks for a fucked-up duck!"
"拿回了子Q砹KX!"
So it's like a limerick.
@像是打油
You didn't think that was funny?
你X得不好笑?
I thought it was entertaining at the end, sure,
我X得最後是U反蟊的 _是
the way all the words were put together,
把所有的~都串在一起
but in terms of content?
但是热萆碚f?
No.
不好笑
Get the check-check from Shen-Shen. Let's get out of here.
Y完~咱走人吧
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
e@ 你搞嘛啊
And cut.
卡